{
  "accent": "",
  "front": "en",
  "cards": [
    {
      "back": "att vara",
      "front": "to be",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag",
      "front": "I",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag är",
      "front": "I am",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en",
      "front": "a, an",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett",
      "front": "a, an",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en pojke",
      "front": "a boy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en flicka",
      "front": "a girl",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en man",
      "front": "a man",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kvinna",
      "front": "a woman",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hon",
      "front": "she",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "han",
      "front": "he",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag äter",
      "front": "I eat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett bröd",
      "front": "bread",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "och",
      "front": "and",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett äpple",
      "front": "an apple",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag dricker",
      "front": "I drink",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(ett) vatten",
      "front": "water",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kvinnan",
      "front": "the woman",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mannen",
      "front": "the man",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) mjölk",
      "front": "milk",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag läser",
      "front": "I read",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en bok",
      "front": "a book",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en meny",
      "front": "a menu",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tidning",
      "front": "a newspaper",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "du",
      "front": "you [singular]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ni",
      "front": "you [plural]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "de",
      "front": "they",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vi",
      "front": "we",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det",
      "front": "it, that [neuter]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "flickor",
      "front": "girls",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "pojkar",
      "front": "boys",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kvinnor",
      "front": "women",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "män",
      "front": "men",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har",
      "front": "I have",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en smörgås",
      "front": "a sandwich",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(ett) ris",
      "front": "rice",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett barn",
      "front": "a child",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett brev",
      "front": "a letter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "pojken",
      "front": "the boy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "flickan",
      "front": "the girl",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "barnet",
      "front": "the child",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hej",
      "front": "hey, hi",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tack",
      "front": "thanks",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ja",
      "front": "yes",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nej",
      "front": "no",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hej då",
      "front": "bye",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "då",
      "front": "then",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tack så mycket",
      "front": "thank you very much",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mycket",
      "front": "very, much, a lot",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "varsågod",
      "front": "you\u0027re welcome",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ursäkta",
      "front": "excuse me, sorry",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hallå",
      "front": "hello",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "snälla",
      "front": "please",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "välkommen",
      "front": "welcome",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "god",
      "front": "good, kind; tasty",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en natt",
      "front": "a night",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en morgon",
      "front": "a morning",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag talar",
      "front": "I speak",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) svenska",
      "front": "Swedish [language]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag talar svenska",
      "front": "I speak Swedish",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) engelska",
      "front": "English [language]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "inte",
      "front": "not",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ej",
      "front": "not [formal]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag älskar",
      "front": "I love",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag tycker om",
      "front": "I like",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en fisk",
      "front": "a fish",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en apelsin",
      "front": "an orange",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(ett) kaffe",
      "front": "coffee",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett ägg",
      "front": "an egg",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kyckling",
      "front": "a chicken",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en dryck",
      "front": "a drink",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en middag",
      "front": "a dinner",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett vin",
      "front": "wine",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(ett) socker",
      "front": "sugar",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en lunch",
      "front": "a lunch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en frukost",
      "front": "a breakfast",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ost",
      "front": "a cheese",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en frukt",
      "front": "a fruit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) pasta",
      "front": "pasta",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) mat",
      "front": "food",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en öl",
      "front": "a beer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(ett) nötkött",
      "front": "beef",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en soppa",
      "front": "a soup",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tomat",
      "front": "a tomato",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en jordgubbe",
      "front": "a strawberry",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en citron",
      "front": "a lemon",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) peppar",
      "front": "pepper",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(ett) salt",
      "front": "salt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) olja",
      "front": "oil",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en måltid",
      "front": "a meal",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(ett) te",
      "front": "tea",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(ett) fläskkött",
      "front": "pork",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en vegetarian",
      "front": "a vegetarian",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(ett) kött",
      "front": "meat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en glass",
      "front": "an ice cream",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en juice",
      "front": "a juice",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett glas",
      "front": "a glass",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en gaffel",
      "front": "a fork",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kniv",
      "front": "a knife",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en sked",
      "front": "a spoon",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kopp",
      "front": "a cup",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tallrik",
      "front": "a plate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en restaurang",
      "front": "a restaurant",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kock",
      "front": "a cook",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kocken",
      "front": "the cook",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "äpplet",
      "front": "the apple",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "glaset",
      "front": "the glass",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "skeden",
      "front": "the spoon",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en katt",
      "front": "a cat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en hund",
      "front": "a dog, hound",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en häst",
      "front": "a horse",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en fågel",
      "front": "a bird",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en björn",
      "front": "a bear",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en älg",
      "front": "an elk, a moose",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett djur",
      "front": "an animal",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en anka",
      "front": "a duck",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en spindel",
      "front": "a spider",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en krabba",
      "front": "a crab",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en sköldpadda",
      "front": "a turtle",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en elefant",
      "front": "an elephant",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en varg",
      "front": "a wolf",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en mus",
      "front": "a mouse",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ren",
      "front": "a reindeer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en myra",
      "front": "an ant",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hunden",
      "front": "the dog, hound",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "katten",
      "front": "the cat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "björnen",
      "front": "the bear",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "myran",
      "front": "the ant",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "spindeln",
      "front": "the spider",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mannen",
      "front": "the man",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kvinnan",
      "front": "the woman",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "pojken",
      "front": "the boy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "flickan",
      "front": "the girl",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "barnet",
      "front": "the child",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "smörgåsen",
      "front": "the sandwich",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kaffet",
      "front": "the coffee",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vinet",
      "front": "the wine",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "frukten",
      "front": "the fruit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "köttet",
      "front": "the meat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "teet",
      "front": "the tea",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ölen",
      "front": "the beer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vattnet",
      "front": "the water",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "apelsinen",
      "front": "the orange",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ägget",
      "front": "the egg",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kycklingen",
      "front": "the chicken",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sockret",
      "front": "the sugar",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "saltet",
      "front": "the salt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "osten",
      "front": "the cheese",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "soppan",
      "front": "the soup",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lunchen",
      "front": "the lunch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "frukosten",
      "front": "the breakfast",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "riset",
      "front": "the rice",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nötköttet",
      "front": "the beef",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vegetarianen",
      "front": "the vegetarian",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "maten",
      "front": "the food",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "pastan",
      "front": "the pasta",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "björnen",
      "front": "the bear",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jordgubben",
      "front": "the strawberry",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "citronen",
      "front": "the lemon",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "pepparn",
      "front": "the pepper",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "oljan",
      "front": "the oil",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hunden",
      "front": "the dog, hound",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "katten",
      "front": "the cat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "myran",
      "front": "the ant",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "spindeln",
      "front": "the spider",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fisken",
      "front": "the fish",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fläskköttet",
      "front": "the pork",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tomaten",
      "front": "the tomato",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "glassen",
      "front": "the ice cream",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tidningen",
      "front": "the newspaper",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "boken",
      "front": "the book",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "brevet",
      "front": "the letter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "brödet",
      "front": "the bread",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "måltiden",
      "front": "the meal",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kocken",
      "front": "the cook",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "äpplet",
      "front": "the apple",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "glaset",
      "front": "the glass",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "skeden",
      "front": "the spoon",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "äpplen",
      "front": "apples",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "böcker",
      "front": "books",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tidningar",
      "front": "newspapers",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "katter",
      "front": "cats",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hundar",
      "front": "dogs, hounds",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hästar",
      "front": "horses",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "flera",
      "front": "several, many",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "brev",
      "front": "letters",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ankor",
      "front": "ducks",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sköldpaddor",
      "front": "turtles",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "djur",
      "front": "animals",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fåglar",
      "front": "birds",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tallrikar",
      "front": "plates",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "smörgåsar",
      "front": "sandwiches",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "elefanter",
      "front": "elephants",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "barn",
      "front": "children",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "äpplena",
      "front": "the apples",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tidningarna",
      "front": "the newspapers",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "katterna",
      "front": "the cats",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hundarna",
      "front": "the dogs, hounds",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "elefanterna",
      "front": "the elephants",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "männen",
      "front": "the men",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kockar",
      "front": "cooks",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kvinnorna",
      "front": "the women",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "möss",
      "front": "mice",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mössen",
      "front": "the mice",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "knivar",
      "front": "knives",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ankorna",
      "front": "the ducks",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sköldpaddorna",
      "front": "the turtles",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "djuren",
      "front": "the animals",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fåglarna",
      "front": "the birds",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tallrikarna",
      "front": "the plates",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "smörgåsarna",
      "front": "the sandwiches",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hästarna",
      "front": "the horses",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "böckerna",
      "front": "the books",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kockarna",
      "front": "the cooks",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "breven",
      "front": "the letters",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "älgarna",
      "front": "the elks",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jordgubbar",
      "front": "strawberries",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jordgubbarna",
      "front": "the strawberries",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fiskar",
      "front": "fish [plural]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fiskarna",
      "front": "the fish [plural]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "flickorna",
      "front": "the girls",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "pojkarna",
      "front": "the boys",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "barnen",
      "front": "the children",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hans",
      "front": "his",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hennes",
      "front": "hers",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "min",
      "front": "my",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mitt",
      "front": "my",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mina",
      "front": "my",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "din",
      "front": "your (du)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ditt",
      "front": "your (du)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dina",
      "front": "your (du)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sin",
      "front": "his/her/its/their",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sitt",
      "front": "his/her/its/their",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sina",
      "front": "his/her/its/their",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vår",
      "front": "our",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vårt",
      "front": "our",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "våra",
      "front": "our",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "er",
      "front": "your (ni)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ert",
      "front": "your (ni)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "era",
      "front": "your (ni)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dess",
      "front": "its",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "deras",
      "front": "their",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "den",
      "front": "it",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det",
      "front": "it",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "henne",
      "front": "her (objective she)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "honom",
      "front": "him (objective he)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mig",
      "front": "me (objective I)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dig",
      "front": "you (obj. you)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "er",
      "front": "you (obj. plural you)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "oss",
      "front": "us (objective we)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dem",
      "front": "them (objective they)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en sko",
      "front": "a shoe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en klänning",
      "front": "a dress",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tröja",
      "front": "a sweater",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en jacka",
      "front": "a jacket",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har på mig",
      "front": "I wear",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "skor",
      "front": "shoes",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en strumpa",
      "front": "a sock",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en byxa",
      "front": "(a pair of) pants, trousers",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) kläder",
      "front": "clothes",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kostym",
      "front": "a suit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en hatt",
      "front": "a hat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en skjorta",
      "front": "a shirt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en handske",
      "front": "a glove",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "handskar",
      "front": "gloves",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en slips",
      "front": "a (neck) tie",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "slipsar",
      "front": "(neck) ties",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ficka",
      "front": "a pocket",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en knapp",
      "front": "a button",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "knappar",
      "front": "buttons",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en halsduk",
      "front": "a scarf",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en rock",
      "front": "a coat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "rockar",
      "front": "coats",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kjol",
      "front": "a skirt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kjolar",
      "front": "skirts",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett skärp",
      "front": "a belt [worn]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kläderna",
      "front": "the clothes",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag ser",
      "front": "I see",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag kommer",
      "front": "I come",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag simmar",
      "front": "I swim",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag skriver",
      "front": "I write",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag sjunger",
      "front": "I sing",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag väljer",
      "front": "I choose",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag går",
      "front": "I go, walk",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag hoppar",
      "front": "I jump, hop",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag lagar mat",
      "front": "I cook, I prepare food",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag sover",
      "front": "I sleep",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag springer",
      "front": "I run",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag åker",
      "front": "I go, travel [via transportation]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det regnar",
      "front": "it rains",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag hör",
      "front": "I hear",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att höra",
      "front": "to hear",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag säljer",
      "front": "I sell",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag betalar",
      "front": "I pay",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag vill",
      "front": "I want",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag vill ha",
      "front": "I want to have",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att vilja",
      "front": "to want",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag hittar",
      "front": "I find",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag arbetar",
      "front": "I work",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag ritar",
      "front": "I draw",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag köper",
      "front": "I buy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag använder",
      "front": "I use",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag visar",
      "front": "I show",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag leker",
      "front": "I play [unstructured] (e.g. with a child, friend, animal)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag skrattar",
      "front": "I laugh",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag gråter",
      "front": "I cry",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag tvättar",
      "front": "I wash, I clean",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag lyssnar",
      "front": "I listen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag står",
      "front": "I stand",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag pratar",
      "front": "I talk",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag flyger",
      "front": "I fly",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det finns",
      "front": "there is/are",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag tar",
      "front": "I take",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag stöttar",
      "front": "I support \u003cbear, hold up\u003e [e.g. a roof]; I support [a team, party, law, statement]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag sitter",
      "front": "I sit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag kan",
      "front": "I can",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att kunna",
      "front": "to be able to",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vit",
      "front": "white",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "grå",
      "front": "grey",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "svart",
      "front": "black",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "röd",
      "front": "red",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "blå",
      "front": "blue",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "grön",
      "front": "green",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "gul",
      "front": "yellow",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "orange",
      "front": "orange",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "rosa",
      "front": "pink, rose pink",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lila",
      "front": "lilac, purple, violet",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "brun",
      "front": "brown",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "gyllene",
      "front": "golden",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en färg",
      "front": "a color, paint",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "färgglad",
      "front": "colorful",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vad?",
      "front": "What?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hur?",
      "front": "How?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vem?",
      "front": "Who?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vems?",
      "front": "Whose?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "varför?",
      "front": "Why?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vart?",
      "front": "Where to?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "var?",
      "front": "Where?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hur många?",
      "front": "How many? [countable]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hur mycket?",
      "front": "How much? [uncountable]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "när?",
      "front": "When?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en fråga",
      "front": "a question",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett svar",
      "front": "an answer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag gör",
      "front": "I do, I make",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ingen",
      "front": "no, none, nobody",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "inget",
      "front": "no, none, nothing",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "inga",
      "front": "no, none",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag förstår",
      "front": "I understand",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag svarar",
      "front": "I answer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag frågar",
      "front": "I ask",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att veta",
      "front": "to know [something]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag vet",
      "front": "I know [something]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vilken?",
      "front": "which, what?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vilket?",
      "front": "which, what?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vilka?",
      "front": "which, what?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jo",
      "front": "yes [negative]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "från",
      "front": "from",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "i",
      "front": "in",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "på",
      "front": "on; at, in",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag går på restaurang",
      "front": "I go to a restaurant",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vid",
      "front": "at, by; beside",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "av",
      "front": "of; from",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mellan",
      "front": "between",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "för",
      "front": "for",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "utan",
      "front": "without",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "med",
      "front": "with",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "genom",
      "front": "through; across",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "till",
      "front": "to(wards); for",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "enligt",
      "front": "according to",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "efter",
      "front": "after; for",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "över",
      "front": "over",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "under",
      "front": "under, underneath; during",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "inne i",
      "front": "inside of",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "utanför",
      "front": "outside of",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "framför",
      "front": "in front of, ahead of",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bakom",
      "front": "behind",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "framåt",
      "front": "forwards, ahead",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bakåt",
      "front": "backwards, to(wards) the rear",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bredvid",
      "front": "next to, beside",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mot",
      "front": "towards",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hos",
      "front": "at, with",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "före",
      "front": "in front of; before",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "åt",
      "front": "towards; to, for (i.e. when helping/doing a favour)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "om",
      "front": "if",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "eller",
      "front": "or",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "men",
      "front": "but",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "utan",
      "front": "but [negative]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "medan",
      "front": "while",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "innan",
      "front": "before [in time]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "när",
      "front": "when",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "när som helst",
      "front": "whenever, at any time",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "som",
      "front": "like, as",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "eftersom",
      "front": "because, since",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "därför",
      "front": "therefore, consequently",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "därför att",
      "front": "because, since",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att",
      "front": "that; to [infinitive marker]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "för att",
      "front": "in order to",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tid",
      "front": "a time [era, period]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tider",
      "front": "times [eras, periods]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en eftermiddag",
      "front": "an afternoon",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en dag",
      "front": "a day",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dagar",
      "front": "days",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "i dag",
      "front": "today",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kväll",
      "front": "an evening",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kvällar",
      "front": "evenings",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "i kväll",
      "front": "tonight, this evening",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "om",
      "front": "in, within [time]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en timme",
      "front": "an hour",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en morgon",
      "front": "a morning",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "morgnar",
      "front": "mornings",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "i morgon",
      "front": "tomorrow",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nätter",
      "front": "nights",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kalender",
      "front": "a calendar",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kalendrar",
      "front": "calendars",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en måndag",
      "front": "a Monday",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tisdag",
      "front": "a Tuesday",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en onsdag",
      "front": "a Wednesday",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en torsdag",
      "front": "a Thursday",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en fredag",
      "front": "a Friday",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en lördag",
      "front": "a Saturday",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en söndag",
      "front": "a Sunday",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett år",
      "front": "a year",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "i år",
      "front": "this year",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en vecka",
      "front": "a week",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ålder",
      "front": "an age",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "åldrar",
      "front": "ages",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en helg",
      "front": "a weekend; a holiday",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "helger",
      "front": "weekends; holidays",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en månad",
      "front": "a month",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "månader",
      "front": "months",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett datum",
      "front": "a date [calendar]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "januari",
      "front": "January",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "februari",
      "front": "February",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mars",
      "front": "March",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "april",
      "front": "April",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "maj",
      "front": "May",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "juni",
      "front": "June",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "juli",
      "front": "July",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "augusti",
      "front": "August",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "september",
      "front": "September",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "oktober",
      "front": "October",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "november",
      "front": "November",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "december",
      "front": "December",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en vardag",
      "front": "a weekday",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en årstid",
      "front": "a season",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en vår",
      "front": "a spring (season)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vårar",
      "front": "springs (season)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en vinter",
      "front": "a winter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vintrar",
      "front": "winters",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en sommar",
      "front": "a summer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "somrar",
      "front": "summers",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sommaren",
      "front": "the summer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en höst",
      "front": "an autumn",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "höstar",
      "front": "autumns",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en minut",
      "front": "a minute",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "minuter",
      "front": "minutes",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en midsommar",
      "front": "a Midsummer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en period",
      "front": "a period",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "perioder",
      "front": "periods",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett århundrade",
      "front": "a century",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "århundraden",
      "front": "centuries",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett ögonblick",
      "front": "a moment, a blink of an eye",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "född",
      "front": "born",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag är född",
      "front": "I was born",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett årtionde",
      "front": "a decade",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "årtionden",
      "front": "decades",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en sekund",
      "front": "a second",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sekunder",
      "front": "seconds",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en stund",
      "front": "a while",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tills",
      "front": "until, till",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "inte förrän",
      "front": "not until, not before",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kvart",
      "front": "a quarter (of an hour)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kvartar",
      "front": "quarters (of an hour)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en generation",
      "front": "a generation",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "generationer",
      "front": "generations",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett dygn",
      "front": "a 24 hour period",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett halvår",
      "front": "a half of a year",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en fest",
      "front": "a party, a celebration",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fester",
      "front": "parties, celebrations",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en pappa",
      "front": "a dad, papa",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en mamma",
      "front": "a mum, mama",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en dotter",
      "front": "a daughter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "döttrar",
      "front": "daughters",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en syster",
      "front": "a sister",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "systrar",
      "front": "sisters",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en bror",
      "front": "a brother",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bröder",
      "front": "brothers",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en son",
      "front": "a son",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "söner",
      "front": "sons",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en familj",
      "front": "a family",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "familjer",
      "front": "families",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en förälder",
      "front": "a parent",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "föräldrar",
      "front": "parents",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en fru",
      "front": "a wife",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fruar",
      "front": "wives",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett syskon",
      "front": "a sibling",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en mor",
      "front": "a mother",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en far",
      "front": "a father",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en moster",
      "front": "an aunt [maternal]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mostrar",
      "front": "aunts [maternal]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en morbror",
      "front": "an uncle [maternal]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "morbröder",
      "front": "uncles [maternal]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en faster",
      "front": "an aunt [paternal]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fastrar",
      "front": "aunts [paternal]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en farbror",
      "front": "an uncle [paternal]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "farbröder",
      "front": "uncles [paternal]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett bröllop",
      "front": "a wedding",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "modern",
      "front": "the mother",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fadern",
      "front": "the father",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mödrar",
      "front": "mothers",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fäder",
      "front": "fathers",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en mormor",
      "front": "a grandmother [maternal]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en morfar",
      "front": "a grandfather [maternal]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en farmor",
      "front": "a grandmother [paternal]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en farfar",
      "front": "a grandfather [paternal]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kusin",
      "front": "a cousin",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kusiner",
      "front": "cousins",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tvilling",
      "front": "a twin",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tvillingar",
      "front": "twins",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tvillingbror",
      "front": "a twin brother",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tvillingsyster",
      "front": "a twin sister",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett barnbarn",
      "front": "a grandchild",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en svärson",
      "front": "a son-in-law",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en svärdotter",
      "front": "a daughter-in-law",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag heter",
      "front": "I am called, my name is",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en student",
      "front": "a student",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "studenter",
      "front": "students",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en läkare",
      "front": "a doctor",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett arbete",
      "front": "a job, (a) work",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en författare",
      "front": "an author",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en modell",
      "front": "a model",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "modeller",
      "front": "models",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett jobb",
      "front": "a job",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en personal",
      "front": "a staff, personnel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en polis",
      "front": "a police officer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "poliser",
      "front": "police officers",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tolk",
      "front": "an interpreter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tolkar",
      "front": "interpreters",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en advokat",
      "front": "a lawyer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "advokater",
      "front": "lawyers",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en karriär",
      "front": "a career",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "karriärer",
      "front": "careers",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en artist",
      "front": "an artist",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "artister",
      "front": "artists",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en sekreterare",
      "front": "a secretary",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en arbetare",
      "front": "a worker",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "professionell",
      "front": "professional",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en domare",
      "front": "a judge",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en brandman",
      "front": "a firefighter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en pilot",
      "front": "a pilot",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "piloter",
      "front": "pilots",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en vakt",
      "front": "a guard",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vakter",
      "front": "guards",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en skådespelare",
      "front": "an actor",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en skådespelerska",
      "front": "an actress",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en chef",
      "front": "a boss",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "chefer",
      "front": "bosses",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en soldat",
      "front": "a soldier",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "soldater",
      "front": "soldiers",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett yrke",
      "front": "a profession",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en bonde",
      "front": "a farmer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bönder",
      "front": "farmers",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en arkitekt",
      "front": "an architect",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "arkitekter",
      "front": "architects",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ingenjör",
      "front": "an engineer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ingenjörer",
      "front": "engineers",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en präst",
      "front": "a priest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "präster",
      "front": "priests",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "stor",
      "front": "big",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lång",
      "front": "tall, long",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "trött",
      "front": "tired",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "liten",
      "front": "little, small",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "litet",
      "front": "little, small",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "små",
      "front": "little, small",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lilla",
      "front": "little, small",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lille",
      "front": "little, small",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "egen",
      "front": "own",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "eget",
      "front": "own",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "egna",
      "front": "own",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "öppen",
      "front": "open",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "öppet",
      "front": "open",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "öppna",
      "front": "open",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bra",
      "front": "good",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dålig",
      "front": "bad",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kall",
      "front": "cold",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "varm",
      "front": "warm",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ren",
      "front": "clean, pure",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "smutsig",
      "front": "dirty",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vänster",
      "front": "left [direction]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ny",
      "front": "new",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nytt",
      "front": "new",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nya",
      "front": "new",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "gammal",
      "front": "old",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "gammalt",
      "front": "old",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "gamla",
      "front": "old",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fin",
      "front": "fine, nice, pretty",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hel",
      "front": "whole, entire",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lik",
      "front": "alike, similar",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "samma",
      "front": "the same",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "olik",
      "front": "different",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "rätt",
      "front": "right, correct",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fel",
      "front": "wrong",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "riktig",
      "front": "real",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vanlig",
      "front": "normal, common, usual",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "möjlig",
      "front": "possible",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "omöjlig",
      "front": "impossible",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "konstig",
      "front": "strange, weird",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "viktig",
      "front": "important",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "allvarlig",
      "front": "serious",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ovanlig",
      "front": "unusual",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "självständig",
      "front": "independent",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nödvändig",
      "front": "necessary",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "personlig",
      "front": "personal",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "privat",
      "front": "private",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "populär",
      "front": "popular",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nästa",
      "front": "next",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sist",
      "front": "last",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vacker",
      "front": "beautiful, pretty",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vackert",
      "front": "beautiful, pretty",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vackra",
      "front": "beautiful, pretty",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ful",
      "front": "ugly, foul",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "full",
      "front": "full; drunk",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tom",
      "front": "empty",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "perfekt",
      "front": "perfect",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "utmärkt",
      "front": "excellent",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "intressant",
      "front": "interesting",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "modern",
      "front": "modern",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "officiell",
      "front": "official",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dyr",
      "front": "expensive, dear",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "rik",
      "front": "rich",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "religiös",
      "front": "religious",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "historisk",
      "front": "historical",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "snygg",
      "front": "handsome, good-looking, beautiful",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ledsen",
      "front": "sad, sorry",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "berömd",
      "front": "famous",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "effektiv",
      "front": "efficient; effective",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "särskild",
      "front": "special; particular",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vegetarisk",
      "front": "vegetarian",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "traditionell",
      "front": "traditional",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "rädd",
      "front": "afraid",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bekväm",
      "front": "comfortable",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jätte-",
      "front": "super-, very-",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jättebra",
      "front": "very good",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "värdefull",
      "front": "valuable, precious",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tvåspråkig",
      "front": "bilingual",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag är rädd för...",
      "front": "I am afraid of...",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har det bekvämt",
      "front": "I\u0027m comfortable",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Vad är det för fel på dig?",
      "front": "What is wrong with you?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att ha rätt/fel",
      "front": "to be correct/incorrect",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag hade rätt",
      "front": "I was right",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "du hade fel",
      "front": "you were wrong",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag öppnar",
      "front": "I open",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag ger",
      "front": "I give",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag tänker",
      "front": "I think, ponder, imagine; I plan to",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag ringer",
      "front": "I call, ring",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag räddar",
      "front": "I save, rescue",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag ser",
      "front": "I see",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag ser ut \u003csom\u003e",
      "front": "I look \u003clike\u003e",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag studerar",
      "front": "I study",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag håller",
      "front": "I hold",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag lever",
      "front": "I live, am alive",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag tittar \u003cpå\u003e",
      "front": "I watch, look \u003cat\u003e",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag bjuder",
      "front": "I offer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag hinner",
      "front": "I have time; I am on time",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag försöker",
      "front": "I try [attempt to, make an effort]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag presenterar",
      "front": "I present",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag presenterar mig",
      "front": "I introduce myself",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag behöver",
      "front": "I need",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag ligger",
      "front": "I lie down",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag bor",
      "front": "I live, inhabit [somewhere]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag får",
      "front": "I get to, I may; I get, I receive",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det stämmer",
      "front": "it\u0027s right",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag känner",
      "front": "I know [someone]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag slutar",
      "front": "I finish, I stop",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag kysser",
      "front": "I kiss [passionately]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag önskar",
      "front": "I wish",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag lär",
      "front": "I teach",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att lära",
      "front": "to teach",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag lär mig",
      "front": "I learn",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att lära sig",
      "front": "to learn",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag orkar",
      "front": "I have energy; I can be bothered",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag letar efter",
      "front": "I look/search for",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag passerar",
      "front": "I pass (by)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag tror",
      "front": "I believe (think)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag hjälper",
      "front": "I help",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det räcker",
      "front": "it suffices",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag dör",
      "front": "I die",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag följde",
      "front": "I followed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag tackar",
      "front": "I thank",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det verkar",
      "front": "it seems",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag kramar",
      "front": "I hug",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag säger",
      "front": "I say",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag fryser",
      "front": "I freeze, am cold",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag vilar",
      "front": "I rest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag börjar",
      "front": "I begin, start",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag stannar",
      "front": "I stay/stop [somewhere]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag litar på",
      "front": "I trust, rely on",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag undrar",
      "front": "I wonder",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "också",
      "front": "also, too",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "för",
      "front": "too [excessive]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "långt",
      "front": "far",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nu",
      "front": "now",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "där",
      "front": "there [location]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mer",
      "front": "more [uncountable]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "väldigt",
      "front": "very, enormously",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vanligt",
      "front": "usual",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "som vanligt",
      "front": "as usual",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "aldrig",
      "front": "never",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "här",
      "front": "here [location]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ganska",
      "front": "quite, fairly",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "alltid",
      "front": "always",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fortfarande",
      "front": "still",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ofta",
      "front": "often",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bara",
      "front": "only, just",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kanske",
      "front": "maybe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "inte ens",
      "front": "not even",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "både ... och",
      "front": "both ... and",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "till och med",
      "front": "up to and including; even",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ändå",
      "front": "yet, still, anyway",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bort",
      "front": "away, off",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sällan",
      "front": "seldom, rarely",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "igen",
      "front": "again",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ibland",
      "front": "sometimes",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "verkligen",
      "front": "really [a lot]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "egentligen",
      "front": "really [actually, in fact]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "än",
      "front": "yet; still; than [comparative]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "redan",
      "front": "already",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "åtminstone",
      "front": "at least",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "borta",
      "front": "away, gone, lost",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hit",
      "front": "here [direction]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "senare",
      "front": "later",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "snart",
      "front": "soon",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "slut",
      "front": "over; used up, all gone, sold out; tired, exhausted",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag är helt slut",
      "front": "I am absolutely exhausted.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tillräckligt",
      "front": "enough, sufficiently",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vanligtvis",
      "front": "usually, normally",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dit",
      "front": "there [direction]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "för närvarande",
      "front": "currently, presently",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "särskilt",
      "front": "especially",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "inte särskilt",
      "front": "not especially; not very",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nästan",
      "front": "almost",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sent",
      "front": "late",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "äntligen",
      "front": "finally",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "faktiskt",
      "front": "actually, in fact",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "helt",
      "front": "completely, entirely; absolutely",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ungefär",
      "front": "approximately, about",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "precis",
      "front": "exactly, precisely",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tydligt",
      "front": "clearly, plainly",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "möjligtvis",
      "front": "possibly",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nära",
      "front": "near, close",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "definitivt",
      "front": "definitely",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "var som helst",
      "front": "wherever, anywhere",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "inte ... heller",
      "front": "not ... either",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "varken A eller B",
      "front": "neither A nor B",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "långsamt",
      "front": "slowly",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tillsammans",
      "front": "together",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "isär",
      "front": "apart",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nödvändigtvis",
      "front": "necessarily",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "troligtvis",
      "front": "\"believably\" - probably, very likely",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "absolut",
      "front": "absolutely",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "i allmänhet",
      "front": "generally",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "där borta",
      "front": "over there [direction]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett hus",
      "front": "a house",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett hotell",
      "front": "a hotel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en lägenhet",
      "front": "a flat, an appartment",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett rum",
      "front": "a room",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "rummet",
      "front": "the room",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett badrum",
      "front": "a bathroom",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett kök",
      "front": "a kitchen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Sverige",
      "front": "Sweden",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en strand",
      "front": "a beach",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "stränder",
      "front": "beaches",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en väg",
      "front": "a road, way",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vägar",
      "front": "roads, ways",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kyrka",
      "front": "a church",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en plats",
      "front": "a place, spot",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "platser",
      "front": "places, spots",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en flygplats",
      "front": "an airport",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en stad",
      "front": "a city, a town",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "staden",
      "front": "the city",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "städer",
      "front": "cities",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett land",
      "front": "a country, land",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "länder",
      "front": "countries, lands",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Finland",
      "front": "Finland",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett hem",
      "front": "a home",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hem",
      "front": "home [direction]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hemma",
      "front": "(at) home [location]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "längs",
      "front": "along",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en gata",
      "front": "a street",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett slott",
      "front": "a castle",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en trädgård",
      "front": "a garden",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "trädgårdar",
      "front": "gardens",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en adress",
      "front": "an address",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en avdelning",
      "front": "a department",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en marknad",
      "front": "a market",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "marknader",
      "front": "markets",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en park",
      "front": "a park",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "parker",
      "front": "parks",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett kontor",
      "front": "an office",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett område",
      "front": "an area",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en bank",
      "front": "a bank",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "banker",
      "front": "banks",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ö",
      "front": "an island",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "öar",
      "front": "islands",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en sjö",
      "front": "a lake",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sjöar",
      "front": "lakes",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en bar",
      "front": "a bar, pub",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "barer",
      "front": "bars, pubs",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "i centrum",
      "front": "downtown, in the city centre",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en region",
      "front": "a region",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "regioner",
      "front": "regions",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en bastu",
      "front": "a sauna",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bastur",
      "front": "saunas",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en mark",
      "front": "a ground; a field",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "marker",
      "front": "grounds; fields",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en dal",
      "front": "a valley",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dalar",
      "front": "valleys",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett museum",
      "front": "a museum",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "museet",
      "front": "the museum",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "museer",
      "front": "museums",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kust",
      "front": "a coast",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kuster",
      "front": "coasts",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en insida",
      "front": "an inside",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en skog",
      "front": "a forest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "skogar",
      "front": "forests",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en byggnad",
      "front": "a building",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "byggnader",
      "front": "buildings",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett hörn",
      "front": "a corner",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en gräns",
      "front": "a border",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "gränser",
      "front": "borders",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett torn",
      "front": "a tower",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en bio",
      "front": "a movie theater",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "biografer",
      "front": "movie theaters",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en allé",
      "front": "an avenue",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "alléer",
      "front": "avenues",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en egendom",
      "front": "a property, a possession",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "egendomar",
      "front": "properties, possessions",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en affär",
      "front": "a shop, store; an affair",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "affärer",
      "front": "shops, stores; affairs",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett fängelse",
      "front": "a prison, a jail",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fängelser",
      "front": "prisons, jails",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett palats",
      "front": "a palace",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en huvudstad",
      "front": "a capital city",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en hamn",
      "front": "a port, a harbor",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hamnar",
      "front": "ports, harbors",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "höger",
      "front": "right (direction)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "till höger",
      "front": "on the right, to the right",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "till vänster",
      "front": "on the left, to the left",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en fabrik",
      "front": "a factory",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fabriker",
      "front": "factories",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett torg",
      "front": "a city square, a market",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "väster",
      "front": "west",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "västra",
      "front": "western",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett nöjesfält",
      "front": "an amusement park",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en bondgård",
      "front": "a farm",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) norr",
      "front": "(a) north",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "norra",
      "front": "northern",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en framsida",
      "front": "a front side",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en toalett",
      "front": "a toilet",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "toaletter",
      "front": "toilets",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett fönster",
      "front": "a window",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en säng",
      "front": "a bed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sängar",
      "front": "beds",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en flaska",
      "front": "a bottle, flask",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett bord",
      "front": "a table",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en stol",
      "front": "a chair",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "stolar",
      "front": "chairs",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en möbel",
      "front": "a (piece of) furniture",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "möbler",
      "front": "furniture (plural)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en dörr",
      "front": "a door",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dörrar",
      "front": "doors",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tv",
      "front": "a tv",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tv:n",
      "front": "the tv",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en spegel",
      "front": "a mirror",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "speglar",
      "front": "mirrors",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en radio",
      "front": "a radio",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "radior",
      "front": "radios",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en klocka",
      "front": "a clock",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en mobil",
      "front": "a mobile, cellphone",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mobiler",
      "front": "mobiles, cellphones",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en dator",
      "front": "a computer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "datorer",
      "front": "computers",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en soffa",
      "front": "a sofa, couch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett skrivbord",
      "front": "a desk",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett batteri",
      "front": "a battery",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "batterier",
      "front": "batteries",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en lampa",
      "front": "a lamp",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en flagga",
      "front": "a flag",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tvål",
      "front": "a soap",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tvålar",
      "front": "soaps",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en korg",
      "front": "a basket",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "korgar",
      "front": "baskets",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en skärm",
      "front": "a screen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "skärmar",
      "front": "screens",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en rakhyvel",
      "front": "a razor",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "rakhyvlar",
      "front": "razors",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en plånbok",
      "front": "a wallet",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett lakan",
      "front": "a bedsheet",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en väska",
      "front": "a bag",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en vägg",
      "front": "a wall",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "väggar",
      "front": "walls",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en låda",
      "front": "a box",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en leksak",
      "front": "a toy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en sak",
      "front": "a thing, an object",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "saker",
      "front": "things, objects",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett paraply",
      "front": "an umbrella",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "paraplyer",
      "front": "umbrellas",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tandkräm",
      "front": "a toothpaste",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tandkrämer",
      "front": "toothpastes",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en våning",
      "front": "a storey [building]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett golv",
      "front": "a floor",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) pengar",
      "front": "money",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en telefon",
      "front": "a telephone",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "telefoner",
      "front": "telephones",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en nyckel",
      "front": "a key",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nycklar",
      "front": "keys",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett tak",
      "front": "a roof, ceiling",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett skåp",
      "front": "a cabinet, a cupboard",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett hjul",
      "front": "a wheel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett täcke",
      "front": "a quilt, a duvet",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kudde",
      "front": "a pillow",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en stekpanna",
      "front": "a frying pan",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en sax",
      "front": "a pair of scissors",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "saxar",
      "front": "(multiple) pairs of scissors",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en pool",
      "front": "a swimming pool",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "pooler",
      "front": "swimming pools",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett papper",
      "front": "a (sheet of) paper; document",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en motor",
      "front": "an engine, motor",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "motorer",
      "front": "engines, motors",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en bit",
      "front": "a bit, piece",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bitar",
      "front": "bits, pieces",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett snöre",
      "front": "a string, a cord",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en maskin",
      "front": "a machine",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "maskiner",
      "front": "machines",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett föremål",
      "front": "an object, a thing",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en hylla",
      "front": "a shelf",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kam",
      "front": "a comb",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kammar",
      "front": "combs",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kedja",
      "front": "a chain",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett pulver",
      "front": "a powder",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en roman",
      "front": "a novel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "romaner",
      "front": "novels",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en duk",
      "front": "a tablecloth",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dukar",
      "front": "tablecloths",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en handduk",
      "front": "a towel (for the hands)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en skål",
      "front": "a bowl",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "skålar",
      "front": "bowls",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tandborste",
      "front": "a toothbrush",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett tyg",
      "front": "a cloth, fabric; (an) equipment",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kastrull",
      "front": "a saucepan",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kastruller",
      "front": "saucepans",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en matta",
      "front": "a carpet, rug, mat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en garderob",
      "front": "a wardrobe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "garderober",
      "front": "wardrobes",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en gardin",
      "front": "a curtain",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "gardiner",
      "front": "curtains",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en fiende",
      "front": "an enemy, fiend",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fiender",
      "front": "enemies, fiends",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett spädbarn",
      "front": "a baby",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en person",
      "front": "a person",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "personer",
      "front": "people",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en vän",
      "front": "a friend",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vänner",
      "front": "friends",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en gäst",
      "front": "a guest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "gäster",
      "front": "guests",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) allmänhet",
      "front": "(a) public",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kommitté",
      "front": "a committee",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kommittéer",
      "front": "committees",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tjej",
      "front": "a girl",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tjejer",
      "front": "girls",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kille",
      "front": "a guy, lad",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kultur",
      "front": "a culture",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kulturer",
      "front": "cultures",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en människa",
      "front": "a human being, a person",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en befolkning",
      "front": "a population",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ungdom",
      "front": "a youth",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ungdomar",
      "front": "youths",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en konferens",
      "front": "a conference",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "konferenser",
      "front": "conferences",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett par",
      "front": "a couple, pair",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en individ",
      "front": "an individual",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "individer",
      "front": "individuals",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett offer",
      "front": "a sacrifice; a victim",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett förhållande",
      "front": "a relationship",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en by",
      "front": "a village",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "byar",
      "front": "villages",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en medborgare",
      "front": "a citizen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en dam",
      "front": "a lady",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "damer",
      "front": "ladies",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(ett) folk",
      "front": "(a) people, folk",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kung",
      "front": "a king",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kungar",
      "front": "kings",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en drottning",
      "front": "a queen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en prins",
      "front": "a prince",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "prinsar",
      "front": "princes",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en vuxen",
      "front": "an adult, a grown-up",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vuxna",
      "front": "adults, grown-ups",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vuxen",
      "front": "adult",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en viking",
      "front": "a viking",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en prinsessa",
      "front": "a princess",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kronprinsessa",
      "front": "a crown princess",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag reser",
      "front": "I travel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag kör",
      "front": "I drive",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det svänger",
      "front": "it turns",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "utomlands",
      "front": "abroad",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "runt",
      "front": "around",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "södra",
      "front": "southern",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "amerikansk",
      "front": "American",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kinesisk",
      "front": "Chinese",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dansk",
      "front": "Danish",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "engelsk",
      "front": "English",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "europeisk",
      "front": "European",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "finsk",
      "front": "Finnish",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "isländsk",
      "front": "Icelandic",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tysk",
      "front": "German",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "norsk",
      "front": "Norwegian",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "svensk",
      "front": "Swedish",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "internationell",
      "front": "international",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "finlandssvensk",
      "front": "Finland-Swedish",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Amerika",
      "front": "America",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Kina",
      "front": "China",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Danmark",
      "front": "Denmark",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Europa",
      "front": "Europe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Tyskland",
      "front": "Germany",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Island",
      "front": "Iceland",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Norge",
      "front": "Norway",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Skandinavien",
      "front": "Scandinavia",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Stockholm",
      "front": "Stockholm",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Norden",
      "front": "the Nordic countries",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en bil",
      "front": "a car",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en cykel",
      "front": "a cycle, a bicycle",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en motorcykel",
      "front": "a motorbike, a motorcycle",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en resväska",
      "front": "a suitcase",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en buss",
      "front": "a bus",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett tåg",
      "front": "a train",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en båt",
      "front": "a boat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett flygplan",
      "front": "a plane",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en guide",
      "front": "a guide",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "guider",
      "front": "guides",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ryggsäck",
      "front": "a backpack, a rucksack",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett besök",
      "front": "a visit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en karta",
      "front": "a map",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett skepp",
      "front": "a ship",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett fordon",
      "front": "a vehicle",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en resa",
      "front": "a trip",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en bro",
      "front": "a bridge",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett äventyr",
      "front": "an adventure",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en biljett",
      "front": "a ticket",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tunnelbana",
      "front": "a subway",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en turist",
      "front": "a tourist",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en hållplats",
      "front": "a bus stop, a tram stop",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett pass",
      "front": "a passport",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en semester",
      "front": "a holiday/vacation",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en norrman",
      "front": "a (male) person from Norway",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "norrmän",
      "front": "several (male) people from Norway",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "denna",
      "front": "this, that",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "den här",
      "front": "this (one)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "den där",
      "front": "that (one)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "detta",
      "front": "this, that",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det här",
      "front": "this (one)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det där",
      "front": "that (one)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dessa",
      "front": "these, those",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "de här",
      "front": "these (ones)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "de där",
      "front": "those (ones)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "någon",
      "front": "any, some, anything, something, anyone, someone",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "något",
      "front": "any, some, anything, something",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "några",
      "front": "any, some",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "allting",
      "front": "everything",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "någonting",
      "front": "something, anything",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "utom",
      "front": "except",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "antingen A eller B",
      "front": "either A or B",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "förra",
      "front": "previous, last [NOT final]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "förrförra",
      "front": "the one before the last",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ingenting",
      "front": "nothing",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ingendera",
      "front": "neither one nor the other, none of several alternatives",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "all",
      "front": "all",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "allt",
      "front": "all",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "alla",
      "front": "all",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "varje",
      "front": "every",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "båda",
      "front": "both, either",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "annan",
      "front": "other, another",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "annat",
      "front": "other, another",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "andra",
      "front": "other, another",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sådan",
      "front": "such, such a",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sådant",
      "front": "such, such a",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sådana",
      "front": "such, such a",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "varandra",
      "front": "each other",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "själv",
      "front": "oneself, myself",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "självt",
      "front": "oneself, myself",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "själva",
      "front": "themselves, yourselves, ourselves",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "den själv",
      "front": "itself",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sig själv",
      "front": "him/herself, itself, myself, themself",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vem som helst",
      "front": "anyone, anybody, whoever",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett",
      "front": "one",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "två",
      "front": "two",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tre",
      "front": "three",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fyra",
      "front": "four",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fem",
      "front": "five",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sex",
      "front": "six",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sju",
      "front": "seven",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "åtta",
      "front": "eight",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nio",
      "front": "nine",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tio",
      "front": "ten",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "värd",
      "front": "worth",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fler",
      "front": "more [countable]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mindre",
      "front": "less, smaller",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "halv",
      "front": "half",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en halva",
      "front": "a half, half of",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dubbel",
      "front": "double",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dubbla",
      "front": "double",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dubbel så mycket",
      "front": "twice as much",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sammanlagd",
      "front": "total",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "plus",
      "front": "plus",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "per",
      "front": "per",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "första",
      "front": "first",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "andra",
      "front": "second",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tredje",
      "front": "third",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fjärde",
      "front": "fourth",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "femte",
      "front": "fifth",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sjätte",
      "front": "sixth",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sjunde",
      "front": "seventh",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "åttonde",
      "front": "eighth",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nionde",
      "front": "ninth",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tionde",
      "front": "tenth",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett nummer",
      "front": "a number",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett telefonnummer",
      "front": "a telephone number",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en gång",
      "front": "a time, as in: an occurence",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett antal",
      "front": "an amount, a quantity [countable]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en siffra",
      "front": "a figure, a numeral",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett stycke",
      "front": "a piece, an item",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en mängd",
      "front": "an amount [uncountable]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en summa",
      "front": "a sum",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det kostar",
      "front": "it costs",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en krona",
      "front": "a krona, a crown",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en meter",
      "front": "a meter, a metre",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett genomsnitt",
      "front": "an average",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en majoritet",
      "front": "a majority",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nittonhundratalet",
      "front": "the twentieth century",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "... till",
      "front": "more/another ...",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "elva",
      "front": "eleven",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tolv",
      "front": "twelve",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tretton",
      "front": "thirteen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fjorton",
      "front": "fourteen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "femton",
      "front": "fifteen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sexton",
      "front": "sixteen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sjutton",
      "front": "seventeen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "arton",
      "front": "eighteen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nitton",
      "front": "nineteen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tjugo",
      "front": "twenty",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tjugoett",
      "front": "twenty one",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tjugotvå",
      "front": "twenty two",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tjugotre",
      "front": "twenty three",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tjugofyra",
      "front": "twenty four",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tjugofem",
      "front": "twenty five",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "trettio",
      "front": "thirty",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fyrtio",
      "front": "fourty",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "femtio",
      "front": "fifty",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sextio",
      "front": "sixty",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sjuttio",
      "front": "seventy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "åttio",
      "front": "eighty",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nittio",
      "front": "ninety",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett hundra",
      "front": "a hundred",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett tusen",
      "front": "a thousand",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en miljon",
      "front": "a million",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en miljard",
      "front": "a billion",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett hundratal",
      "front": "(a) hundreds, some hundred",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett tusental",
      "front": "(a) thousands, some thousand",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag respekterar",
      "front": "I respect",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag ställer",
      "front": "I set, I put down",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att innehålla",
      "front": "to contain, to include",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det innehåller",
      "front": "it contains, it includes",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag möter",
      "front": "I meet",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att bli",
      "front": "to become",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag blir",
      "front": "I become",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag räknar",
      "front": "I count, I calculate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag klipper",
      "front": "I cut [i.e. with scissors]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att må",
      "front": "to feel [good or bad]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag mår",
      "front": "I feel [good or bad]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag saknar",
      "front": "I miss, lack [someone/thing]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag missar",
      "front": "I miss [a target], I fail [to attend]; I overlook",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att lägga",
      "front": "to lay down, to put into",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag lägger",
      "front": "I lay down, I put into",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det liknar",
      "front": "it resembles, it compares (to)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag hyr",
      "front": "I rent",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag fyller",
      "front": "I fill, I reach an age",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag tappar",
      "front": "I drop, I lose",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag anser",
      "front": "I consider (think)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag tillverkar",
      "front": "I produce",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag blandar",
      "front": "I mix, I shuffle",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag torkar",
      "front": "I wipe, I dust, I sweep, I (make) dry",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag bokar",
      "front": "I book, I reserve",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att fortsätta",
      "front": "to continue, to proceed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag fortsätter",
      "front": "I continue, I proceed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag bygger",
      "front": "I build, I construct",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag väntar (på)",
      "front": "I wait (for), I expect",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det hänger",
      "front": "it hangs",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag importerar",
      "front": "I import",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag tillbringar",
      "front": "I spend (time)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag berättar",
      "front": "I tell",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag lämnar",
      "front": "I leave",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag undervisar",
      "front": "I teach, I tutor",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det tillhör",
      "front": "it belongs to",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag antar",
      "front": "I suppose, I presume",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag hatar",
      "front": "I hate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det fungerar",
      "front": "It works, It functions",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag skickar",
      "front": "I send; I pass [i.e. something to someone]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag delar",
      "front": "I divide",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag förklarar",
      "front": "I explain",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det passar",
      "front": "it is suitable, it fits (clothes)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag serverar",
      "front": "I serve",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag stänger",
      "front": "I close, I shut",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag besöker",
      "front": "I visit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att vinna",
      "front": "to win, to defeat, to gain, to profit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag vinner",
      "front": "I win, I defeat, I gain, I profit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att skära",
      "front": "to cut [e.g. knife]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag skär",
      "front": "I cut [e.g. knife]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att be",
      "front": "to ask for, to pray for",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag ber",
      "front": "I ask for, I pray for",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag förlorar",
      "front": "I lose",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det angår",
      "front": "it concerns, it involves",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag håller med",
      "front": "I agree",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "håller du med?",
      "front": "Do you agree?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag kommer fram",
      "front": "I arrive, I get there",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag skriver under",
      "front": "I sign",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag lägger till",
      "front": "I add",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag äter upp",
      "front": "I eat all of, I finish (food)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag räknar ut",
      "front": "I figure out",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag dyker upp",
      "front": "I appear, I show up",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag hoppas",
      "front": "I hope",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag misslyckas",
      "front": "I fail",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag lyckas",
      "front": "I succeed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det fattas",
      "front": "It is missing",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag trivs",
      "front": "I am comfortable/satisfied (with a place/situation)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag minns",
      "front": "I remember",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vi ses",
      "front": "See you (later)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag träffas",
      "front": "I meet",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det känns (som om)",
      "front": "It feels (as though)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag skyndar mig",
      "front": "I hurry",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag känner mig",
      "front": "I feel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag lär mig",
      "front": "I learn",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det överraskar mig",
      "front": "It surprises me",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vi gifter oss",
      "front": "We marry",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag förbereder mig",
      "front": "I prepare",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag bryr mig om",
      "front": "I care about",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag tar med mig",
      "front": "I bring with me",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har med mig",
      "front": "I have with me",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag tar av mig",
      "front": "I take off",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag tar på mig",
      "front": "I put on",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har på mig",
      "front": "I am wearing",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag delar med mig",
      "front": "I share",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att betyda",
      "front": "to mean",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det betyder",
      "front": "it means",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "svår",
      "front": "hard, difficult",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en lärare",
      "front": "a teacher",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en utbildning",
      "front": "an education",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en skola",
      "front": "a school",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en penna",
      "front": "a pen, a pencil",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en anteckning",
      "front": "a note",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en lektion",
      "front": "a lesson",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en elev",
      "front": "a pupil, a student",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en rast",
      "front": "a break",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kurs",
      "front": "a course",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett bibliotek",
      "front": "a library",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett prov",
      "front": "a test",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ansökning",
      "front": "an application",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett exempel",
      "front": "an example",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en studie",
      "front": "a study, a report",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en uppsats",
      "front": "a paper, an essay",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett ord",
      "front": "a word",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett kapitel",
      "front": "a chapter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kunskap",
      "front": "(a) knowledge",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en övning",
      "front": "(a) practise",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en idé",
      "front": "an idea",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en klass",
      "front": "a class",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett universitet",
      "front": "a university",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en professor",
      "front": "a professor",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en föreläsning",
      "front": "a lecture",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en förklaring",
      "front": "an explanation",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en presentation",
      "front": "a presentation",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en högskola",
      "front": "a college, a university-college",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en svårighet",
      "front": "(a) difficulty",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en läxa",
      "front": "(a) homework",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en historia",
      "front": "a story",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett mål",
      "front": "a goal, an objective",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en sida",
      "front": "a page",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett dokument",
      "front": "a document",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en rapport",
      "front": "a report",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en undervisning",
      "front": "(a) teaching/training, an education",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "trots att",
      "front": "in spite of, despite that, even though",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag åt",
      "front": "I ate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag drack",
      "front": "I drank",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag talade",
      "front": "I spoke",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag var",
      "front": "I was/were",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag gick",
      "front": "I went (by foot), I walked",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag åkte",
      "front": "I went (by means of transportation)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag pratade",
      "front": "I talked",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag tyckte",
      "front": "I had the opinion (thought)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag tyckte om",
      "front": "I liked",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag älskade",
      "front": "I loved",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det regnade",
      "front": "It rained",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag ville (ha)",
      "front": "I wanted (to have)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag såg",
      "front": "I saw, I looked",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag simmade",
      "front": "I swam",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag kom",
      "front": "I came",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag tappade",
      "front": "I lost, I dropped",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag lekte",
      "front": "I played [unstructured]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag hörde",
      "front": "I heard",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag sade",
      "front": "I said",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag lyssnade",
      "front": "I listened",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag hade",
      "front": "I had",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag arbetade",
      "front": "I worked",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag lagade mat",
      "front": "I cooked",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag gjorde",
      "front": "I did, I made",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag hittade",
      "front": "I found",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag lämnade",
      "front": "I left, gave (up), handed (over) [something]; I left [a place, location]; I abandoned, deserted",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag lämnade tillbaka",
      "front": "I returned [something to its position]; I gave/handed back",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag kom tillbaka",
      "front": "I returned, I got/came back (to something/one)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag berättade",
      "front": "I told",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag lade",
      "front": "I put [into/onto]; I laid (e.g. an object down)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag ställde",
      "front": "I put [onto]; I sat (e.g. an object down)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag tackade",
      "front": "I thanked",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag ringde",
      "front": "I rang, I called",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag tog",
      "front": "I took",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag tänkte",
      "front": "I thought, pondered imagined; I planned",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag skrev",
      "front": "I wrote",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag trodde",
      "front": "I thought [held the belief]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag förlorade",
      "front": "I lost",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag stängde",
      "front": "I closed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag gav",
      "front": "I gave",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag dog",
      "front": "I died",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag stöttade",
      "front": "I supported",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det svängde",
      "front": "It turned",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag sprang",
      "front": "I ran",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag fick",
      "front": "I got, I received, I was allowed to",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag sålde",
      "front": "I sold",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag tittade på",
      "front": "I watched, I looked at",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag kände (mig)",
      "front": "I knew (someone), I felt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag visste",
      "front": "I knew (something)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag letade (efter)",
      "front": "I searched/looked (for)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag behöll",
      "front": "I kept",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag höll",
      "front": "I held",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag höll med",
      "front": "I agreed with",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag vann",
      "front": "I won",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag visade",
      "front": "I showed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag köpte",
      "front": "I bought",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag betalade",
      "front": "I paid",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det hände",
      "front": "It happened",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag presenterade",
      "front": "I presented, I introduced",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag öppnade",
      "front": "I opened",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det verkade",
      "front": "It seemed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag förklarade",
      "front": "I explained",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag svarade",
      "front": "I answered",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag frågade",
      "front": "I asked",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det innehöll",
      "front": "It contained",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det fanns",
      "front": "There was, There were/existed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det dök upp",
      "front": "It showed up, It appeared",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag stannade",
      "front": "I stopped, I stayed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag sov",
      "front": "I slept",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag litade på",
      "front": "I trusted",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag bodde",
      "front": "I lived, I stayed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag väntade",
      "front": "I waited",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag vilade",
      "front": "I rested",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "i morse",
      "front": "this morning",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "i går",
      "front": "yesterday",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "i förrgår",
      "front": "the day before yesterday",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nyligen",
      "front": "recently",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tillbaka",
      "front": "back",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) mitt",
      "front": "middle",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mitt i natten",
      "front": "in the middle of the night",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hela natten",
      "front": "all night",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att bruka",
      "front": "to be used to, to be in the habit of",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att skriva",
      "front": "to write",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att simma",
      "front": "to swim",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att vara",
      "front": "to be",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att gå",
      "front": "to go, to walk [via foot]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att bli",
      "front": "to become",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att se",
      "front": "to see",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att leka",
      "front": "to play [unstructured]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att sova",
      "front": "to sleep",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att springa",
      "front": "to run",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att tycka",
      "front": "to have an opinion about",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att laga",
      "front": "to fix, to repair",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att laga mat",
      "front": "to cook",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att betala",
      "front": "to pay",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att vilja",
      "front": "to want",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att tala",
      "front": "to speak",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att göra",
      "front": "to do, to make",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att använda",
      "front": "to use",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att åka",
      "front": "to go, to travel [via transportation]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att rita",
      "front": "to draw",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att bestämma",
      "front": "to decide",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att stänga",
      "front": "to close, to shut",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att hyra",
      "front": "to rent",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att regna",
      "front": "to rain",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att höra",
      "front": "to hear",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att lyssna",
      "front": "to listen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att säga",
      "front": "to say",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att äta",
      "front": "to eat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att berätta",
      "front": "to tell",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att få",
      "front": "to get, to receive, to be allowed to",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att hitta",
      "front": "to find",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att träna",
      "front": "to practice, to exercise",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att hjälpa",
      "front": "to help",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att minnas",
      "front": "to remember",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att stanna",
      "front": "to stay, stop",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att arbeta",
      "front": "to work",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att köpa",
      "front": "to buy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att veta",
      "front": "to know [something]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att ta",
      "front": "to take",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att behöva",
      "front": "to need",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att tvätta",
      "front": "to wash, to clean",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att sjunga",
      "front": "to sing",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att visa",
      "front": "to show",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att öppna",
      "front": "to open",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att tänka",
      "front": "to think, ponder, imagine; to plan to",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att tro",
      "front": "to think [as in hold a belief]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att ringa",
      "front": "to call, to ring",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att hålla",
      "front": "to hold",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att fånga",
      "front": "to catch, to capture",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att ge",
      "front": "to give",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att studera",
      "front": "to study",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att lära",
      "front": "to teach",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att lära sig",
      "front": "to learn",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att komma",
      "front": "to come",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att titta (på)",
      "front": "to look (at)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att bo",
      "front": "to live, inhabit [somewhere]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att börja",
      "front": "to begin",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att sälja",
      "front": "to sell",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att försöka",
      "front": "to try [make an effort]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att fråga",
      "front": "to ask, to question",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att fortsätta",
      "front": "to continue",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att läsa",
      "front": "to read",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att be",
      "front": "to beg, to pray, to request",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att svara",
      "front": "to answer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "öster",
      "front": "east",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Köpenhamn",
      "front": "Copenhagen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Helsingfors",
      "front": "Helsinki",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Göteborg",
      "front": "Gothenburg",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Malmö",
      "front": "Malmo",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Nordeuropa",
      "front": "Northern Europe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Sydeuropa",
      "front": "Southern Europe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Nordamerika",
      "front": "Northern America",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Sydamerika",
      "front": "Southern America",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Östersjön",
      "front": "The Baltic Sea",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Åland",
      "front": "The Aland Islands",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en same",
      "front": "A Sami person",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "samisk",
      "front": "sami",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Frankrike",
      "front": "France",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Polen",
      "front": "Poland",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Grekland",
      "front": "Greece",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Spanien",
      "front": "Spain",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Italien",
      "front": "Italy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Österrike",
      "front": "Austria",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Storbritannien",
      "front": "Great Britain",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Ryssland",
      "front": "Russia",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Nederländerna",
      "front": "The Netherlands",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Brasilien",
      "front": "Brazil",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fransk",
      "front": "French",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "polsk",
      "front": "Polish",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "grekisk",
      "front": "Greek",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "spansk",
      "front": "Spanish",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "italiensk",
      "front": "Italian",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "österrikisk",
      "front": "Austrian",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "brittisk",
      "front": "British",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "rysk",
      "front": "Russian",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nederländsk",
      "front": "Dutch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "brasiliansk",
      "front": "Brazilian",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Paris",
      "front": "Paris",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Warszawa",
      "front": "Warsaw",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Aten",
      "front": "Athens",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Madrid",
      "front": "Madrid",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Rom",
      "front": "Rome",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Wien",
      "front": "Vienna",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "London",
      "front": "London",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Moskva",
      "front": "Moscow",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Amsterdam",
      "front": "Amsterdam",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Brasilia",
      "front": "Brasilia",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag stod",
      "front": "I stood",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag förstod",
      "front": "I understood",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det räckte",
      "front": "It sufficed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag började",
      "front": "I began, I started",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag försökte",
      "front": "I tried [made an effort]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag bestämde",
      "front": "I decided",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag slutade",
      "front": "I stopped (not stayed)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag antog",
      "front": "I supposed, I presumed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag satt",
      "front": "I sat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag låg",
      "front": "I lay",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag hjälpte",
      "front": "I helped",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag lärde",
      "front": "I taught",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag lärde mig",
      "front": "I learned",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag använde",
      "front": "I used",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag följde",
      "front": "I followed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag läste",
      "front": "I read",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag behövde",
      "front": "I needed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag liknade",
      "front": "I resembled",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag hyrde",
      "front": "I rented",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det torkade",
      "front": "It dried",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag kunde",
      "front": "I could",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag hängde",
      "front": "I hung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag levde",
      "front": "I lived",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag valde",
      "front": "I chose",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag glömde",
      "front": "I forgot",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag lät",
      "front": "I let",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag mindes",
      "front": "I remembered",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag kändes",
      "front": "I knew [someone]; I felt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag hette",
      "front": "I was called",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag blev",
      "front": "I became",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag hamnade",
      "front": "I ended up",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag brukade",
      "front": "I used to",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag körde",
      "front": "I drove",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag sjöng",
      "front": "I sung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag flög",
      "front": "I flew",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag bjöd",
      "front": "I offered, I invited",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag föll",
      "front": "I fell",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag hoppades",
      "front": "I hoped",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nittiotalet",
      "front": "The Nineties",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sjuttiotalet",
      "front": "The Seventies",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag bakar",
      "front": "I bake",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag smakar",
      "front": "I taste",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kaka",
      "front": "a small cake, a cookie",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en bulle",
      "front": "a bun",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) kanel",
      "front": "(a) cinnamon",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kanelbulle",
      "front": "a cinnamon bun",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en fika",
      "front": "a coffee/tea break, usually with cakes/buns",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en sill",
      "front": "a herring",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en potatis",
      "front": "a potato",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en bagare",
      "front": "a baker",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kräfta",
      "front": "a crayfish",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett bageri",
      "front": "a bakery",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett knäckebröd",
      "front": "a crispbread",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett bär",
      "front": "a berry",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett hallon",
      "front": "a raspberry",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) grädde",
      "front": "(a) cream",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en sås",
      "front": "a sauce",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(ett) smör",
      "front": "(a) butter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) margarin",
      "front": "(a) margarine",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en köttbulle",
      "front": "a meatball",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) senap",
      "front": "(a) mustard",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) surströmming",
      "front": "(a) fermented herring",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tårta",
      "front": "a cake [big/decorative]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "törstig",
      "front": "thirsty",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hungrig",
      "front": "hungry",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett kylskåp",
      "front": "a refrigerator",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en osthyvel",
      "front": "a cheese slicer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en korv",
      "front": "a sausage",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en vitlök",
      "front": "a garlic",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en lök",
      "front": "an onion",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en lax",
      "front": "a salmon",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett rödvin",
      "front": "a red wine",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en morot",
      "front": "a carrot",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "morötter",
      "front": "carrots",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en saft",
      "front": "a juice, a squash, a cordial",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Gott nytt år!",
      "front": "Happy New Year!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lycklig",
      "front": "happy; fortunate, lucky",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "olycklig",
      "front": "sad, unfortunate; unlucky",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tursam",
      "front": "lucky, fortunate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "rolig",
      "front": "funny/amusing, enjoyable",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "orolig",
      "front": "anxious, nervous",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tråkig",
      "front": "boring, unfortunate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sorglig",
      "front": "sorrowful, tragic",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "glad",
      "front": "happy, glad",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "känslig",
      "front": "sensitive",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vemodig",
      "front": "wistful, melancholic",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "arg",
      "front": "angry",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en sorg",
      "front": "a sorrow, a grief",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sur",
      "front": "moody, grumpy, sour",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hemsk",
      "front": "terrible",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "snäll",
      "front": "kind, friendly",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fridfull",
      "front": "peaceful",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nervös",
      "front": "nervous, anxious",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "galen",
      "front": "mad, crazy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kul",
      "front": "fun, enjoyable, amusing",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kär",
      "front": "dear, loved, in love",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mysig",
      "front": "cosy, comfortable",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nöjd",
      "front": "content, satisfied",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) lycka",
      "front": "joy, happiness",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett skratt",
      "front": "a laugh, laughter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en känsla",
      "front": "a feeling, a mood",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(ett) vemod",
      "front": "melancholy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) ilska",
      "front": "anger",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett leende",
      "front": "a smile",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) frid",
      "front": "peace [religious, legal etc.]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) kärlek",
      "front": "love",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tår",
      "front": "a tear",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en sambo",
      "front": "a coinhabitant",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag sörjer",
      "front": "I mourn",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag ler",
      "front": "I smile",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag vågar",
      "front": "I dare",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag förlåter",
      "front": "I forgive",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag myser",
      "front": "I am cosy/comfortable",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag gillar",
      "front": "I like",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag oroar mig",
      "front": "I worry",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag kommer inte ihåg",
      "front": "I do not remember",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en del",
      "front": "a {deal}, part",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett namn",
      "front": "a name",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en lista",
      "front": "a list",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett system",
      "front": "a system",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en åsikt",
      "front": "a view [opinion]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett liv",
      "front": "a life",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en service",
      "front": "a service",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en grupp",
      "front": "a group",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett sätt",
      "front": "a way [of doing something]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en utsikt",
      "front": "a view [of an area]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en sort",
      "front": "a sort, a kind",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en order",
      "front": "an order [product/service], a command",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ordning",
      "front": "an order [sequence], (a) tidiness",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en typ",
      "front": "a {type}",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en design",
      "front": "a design",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) kontroll",
      "front": "(a) control, a remote",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en medlem",
      "front": "a member",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en förändring",
      "front": "a change",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en nivå",
      "front": "a level",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett samtal",
      "front": "a conversation, a phone call",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en profil",
      "front": "a profile",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett fall",
      "front": "a case; a fall [i.e. over]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en bild",
      "front": "a picture, an image",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en beskrivning",
      "front": "a description",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(ett) värde",
      "front": "(a) worth, a value",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(ett) innehåll",
      "front": "(a) content",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kategori",
      "front": "a category",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en version",
      "front": "a version",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett konto",
      "front": "an account",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett problem",
      "front": "a problem",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett val",
      "front": "a choice, an option",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett resultat",
      "front": "a result",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) utrustning",
      "front": "(an) equipment",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en aktivitet",
      "front": "an activity",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett förslag",
      "front": "a suggestion",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en sida",
      "front": "a page, a side, a website",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en lösning",
      "front": "a solution",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en överenskommelse",
      "front": "an agreement",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tur",
      "front": "a turn, a tour, (a) luck",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett ansvar",
      "front": "a responsibility",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en början",
      "front": "a beginning",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett ärende",
      "front": "an errand, a case",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett alternativ",
      "front": "an alternative",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en effekt",
      "front": "an effect",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tanke",
      "front": "a thought",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en önskan",
      "front": "a wish",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en dröm",
      "front": "a dream",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett hopp",
      "front": "a hope, a hop/jump",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett beslut",
      "front": "a decision",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett slut",
      "front": "an end, an ending",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en röst",
      "front": "a voice, a vote",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en roll",
      "front": "a role",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en grad",
      "front": "a degree (temperature)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(ett) bevis",
      "front": "(an) evidence, (a) proof",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett syfte",
      "front": "a purpose, an intention",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en möjlighet",
      "front": "a possibility",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en union",
      "front": "a union",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en framgång",
      "front": "a success",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett ämne",
      "front": "a subject, a topic",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett betyg",
      "front": "a grade (education)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en sömn",
      "front": "a sleep",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(ett) mörker",
      "front": "(a) darkness",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett ljus",
      "front": "a light, (a) lightness",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett ställe",
      "front": "a spot, a place",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag hamnar",
      "front": "I end up, I land",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "än",
      "front": "than [comparison], yet/thus far [negative ännu]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "din hund är större än min",
      "front": "Your dog is bigger than mine.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ännu",
      "front": "even [comparison]; yet/thus far [negative]; yet another [additional]; up to a point [still]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har inte sett honom ännu",
      "front": "I have not seen him yet.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har inte sett honom än",
      "front": "I have not seen him yet.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "min bil är ännu bättre!",
      "front": "My car is even better!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "detektiven hittade ännu ett möjligt motiv för mordet",
      "front": "The detective found yet another possible motive for the murder.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det finns hopp ännu",
      "front": "There is yet/still hope.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lite",
      "front": "a little, somewhat, to a small extent",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ung",
      "front": "young",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lik",
      "front": "like, similar to",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kort",
      "front": "short",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "långsam",
      "front": "slow",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "snabb",
      "front": "fast",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fri",
      "front": "free",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ledig",
      "front": "free [available]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "gratis",
      "front": "free [without charge]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lätt",
      "front": "light (weight), easy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "svag",
      "front": "weak",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "stark",
      "front": "strong",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sann",
      "front": "true, according to the truth",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "säker",
      "front": "safe, sure, certain",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "enkel",
      "front": "easy, simple",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "söt",
      "front": "sweet",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "underbar",
      "front": "wonderful",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "djup",
      "front": "deep",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vass",
      "front": "sharp",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fattig",
      "front": "without wealth (poor)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "rättvis",
      "front": "fair, just",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "färdig",
      "front": "ready, prepared",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ensam",
      "front": "alone, lonely",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "trevlig",
      "front": "nice, pleasant",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "viktigare",
      "front": "more important",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "varmare",
      "front": "warmer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kallare",
      "front": "colder",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dyrare",
      "front": "more expensive",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "billigare",
      "front": "cheaper",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tröttare",
      "front": "more tired",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "yngre",
      "front": "younger",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "äldre",
      "front": "older",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nyare",
      "front": "newer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sämre",
      "front": "worse",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bättre",
      "front": "better",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "större",
      "front": "bigger",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "längre",
      "front": "longer, taller, anymore",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "likare",
      "front": "more like",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kortare",
      "front": "shorter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "långsammare",
      "front": "slower",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "snabbare",
      "front": "faster",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "rikare",
      "front": "richer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "finare",
      "front": "finer, nicer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "svårare",
      "front": "harder, more difficult",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "intressantare",
      "front": "more interesting",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vanligare",
      "front": "more common, more usual",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "friare",
      "front": "freer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mindre",
      "front": "smaller, less",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mer",
      "front": "more [uncountable]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lättare",
      "front": "lighter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "oftare",
      "front": "more often",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "svagare",
      "front": "weaker",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "starkare",
      "front": "stronger",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sannare",
      "front": "truer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "säkrare",
      "front": "safer, surer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "enklare",
      "front": "easier, simpler",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sötare",
      "front": "sweeter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "underbarare",
      "front": "more wonderful",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "djupare",
      "front": "deeper",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vassare",
      "front": "sharper",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fattigare",
      "front": "poorer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "rättvisare",
      "front": "fairer, more just",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vackrare",
      "front": "more beautiful",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "färdigare",
      "front": "readier, more prepared",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ensammare",
      "front": "more alone, lonelier",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "trevligare",
      "front": "nicer, more pleasant",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "viktigast",
      "front": "most important",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "varmast",
      "front": "warmest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kallast",
      "front": "coldest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dyrast",
      "front": "most expensive",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "billigast",
      "front": "cheapest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tröttast",
      "front": "most tired",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "yngst",
      "front": "youngest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "äldst",
      "front": "oldest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nyast",
      "front": "newest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sämst",
      "front": "worst [not inherently bad]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bäst",
      "front": "best",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "störst",
      "front": "biggest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "längst",
      "front": "longest, tallest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "likast",
      "front": "most like",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kortast",
      "front": "shortest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "långsammast",
      "front": "slowest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "snabbast",
      "front": "fastest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "rikast",
      "front": "richest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "finast",
      "front": "finest, nicest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "svårast",
      "front": "hardest, most difficult",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "intressantast",
      "front": "most interesting",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vanligast",
      "front": "most common, most usual",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "friast",
      "front": "freest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "minst",
      "front": "smallest, least",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mest",
      "front": "most",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lättast",
      "front": "lightest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "oftast",
      "front": "most often",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "svagast",
      "front": "weakest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "starkast",
      "front": "strongest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sannast",
      "front": "truest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "säkrast",
      "front": "safest, surest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "enklast",
      "front": "easiest, simplest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sötast",
      "front": "sweetest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "underbarast",
      "front": "most wonderful",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "djupast",
      "front": "deepest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vassast",
      "front": "sharpest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fattigast",
      "front": "poorest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "rättvisast",
      "front": "fairest, most just",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vackrast",
      "front": "most beautiful",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "färdigast",
      "front": "readiest, most prepared",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ensammast",
      "front": "most alone, loneliest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "trevligast",
      "front": "nicest, most pleasant",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "trevligt att träffas",
      "front": "Nice to meet (you).",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har",
      "front": "I have",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det har regnat",
      "front": "It has rained",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har haft",
      "front": "I have had",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har läst",
      "front": "I have read",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det har varit",
      "front": "It has been",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har gått",
      "front": "I have gone, walked [via foot]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har lagat",
      "front": "I have fixed, I have cooked",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har velat",
      "front": "I have wanted",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har lekt",
      "front": "I have played [unstructured] (e.g. with a friend/animal)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har hört",
      "front": "I have heard",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har ätit",
      "front": "I have eaten",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har pratat",
      "front": "I have talked",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har kommit",
      "front": "I have come",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har betalat",
      "front": "I have paid",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har sett",
      "front": "I have seen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har sagt",
      "front": "I have said",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har lämnat",
      "front": "I have left",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det har blivit",
      "front": "It has become",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har gett",
      "front": "I have given",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har skrivit",
      "front": "I have written",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har lagt till",
      "front": "I have added",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har ringt",
      "front": "I have called",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har gjort",
      "front": "I have done, I have made",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har fått",
      "front": "I have gotten, I have received",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har tagit",
      "front": "I have taken",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har frågat",
      "front": "I have asked",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har skickat",
      "front": "I have sent",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har tappat",
      "front": "I have lost, I have dropped",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har utvecklat",
      "front": "I have developed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har presenterat",
      "front": "I have presented, I have introduced",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har stängt",
      "front": "I have closed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har träffat",
      "front": "I have met",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har försökt",
      "front": "I have tried [made an effort]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har sovit",
      "front": "I have slept",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har arbetat",
      "front": "I have worked",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har tänkt",
      "front": "I have thought",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har åkt",
      "front": "I have gone, travelled [via transportation]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har följt",
      "front": "I have followed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har simmat",
      "front": "I have swum",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har sjungit",
      "front": "I have sung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har valt",
      "front": "I have chosen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har hoppat",
      "front": "I have jumped",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har tvingat",
      "front": "I have forced",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har berättat",
      "front": "I have told",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har bott",
      "front": "I have lived, I have inhabited",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har beställt",
      "front": "I have ordered",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har öppnat",
      "front": "I have opened",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har vunnit",
      "front": "I have won",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har stannat",
      "front": "I have stopped/stayed [somewhere]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har köpt",
      "front": "I have bought",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har sålt",
      "front": "I have sold",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har känt",
      "front": "I have known [someone]; I have felt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har druckit",
      "front": "I have drunk",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har saknat",
      "front": "I have missed, lacked [someone/thing]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har slutat",
      "front": "I have finished",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har antagit",
      "front": "I have supposed, I have presumed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har tvättat",
      "front": "I have washed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag har stått",
      "front": "I have stood",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "länge",
      "front": "for/during a long time",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sedan",
      "front": "then, afterwards, after this/that",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sedan",
      "front": "since, from the time that",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "förut",
      "front": "before, previously",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en igelkott",
      "front": "a hedgehog",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ko",
      "front": "a cow",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en uggla",
      "front": "an owl",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kanin",
      "front": "a rabbit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en räv",
      "front": "a fox",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett får",
      "front": "a sheep",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en apa",
      "front": "a monkey, an ape",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett lamm",
      "front": "a lamb",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en mygga",
      "front": "a mosquito",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en fluga",
      "front": "a fly",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en gris",
      "front": "a pig",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en insekt",
      "front": "an insect",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en vinge",
      "front": "a wing",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en svans",
      "front": "a tail",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett bi",
      "front": "a bee",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett lejon",
      "front": "a lion",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ekorre",
      "front": "a squirrel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en orm",
      "front": "a snake",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en groda",
      "front": "a frog",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en fjäril",
      "front": "a butterfly",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ödla",
      "front": "a lizard",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tiger",
      "front": "a tiger",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag bet",
      "front": "I bit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag jagar",
      "front": "I hunt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vass",
      "front": "sharp",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kan",
      "front": "can",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "måste",
      "front": "must",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "får",
      "front": "may, be allowed to, get, receive",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "borde",
      "front": "should",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ska",
      "front": "will, shall",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "läs!",
      "front": "read!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ät!",
      "front": "eat!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tänk!",
      "front": "think!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "köp!",
      "front": "buy!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sälj!",
      "front": "sell!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lyssna!",
      "front": "listen!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kom!",
      "front": "come!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "åk!",
      "front": "go/travel!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sjung!",
      "front": "sing!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "betala!",
      "front": "pay!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tro!",
      "front": "believe!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "spring!",
      "front": "run!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "gör!",
      "front": "do/make!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ta!",
      "front": "take!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "skriv!",
      "front": "write!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "följ!",
      "front": "follow!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "öppna!",
      "front": "open!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fråga!",
      "front": "ask/question!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "gå!",
      "front": "go!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fortsätt!",
      "front": "continue!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ge!",
      "front": "give!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "håll!",
      "front": "hold!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "förlåt!",
      "front": "apologise!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vänta!",
      "front": "wait!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ställ!",
      "front": "put/set/place!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lägg!",
      "front": "put/lay!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "svara!",
      "front": "answer!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "möt!",
      "front": "meet!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "se!",
      "front": "see!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hjälp!",
      "front": "help!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ring!",
      "front": "ring/call!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sluta!",
      "front": "stop! [doing something]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "oroa!",
      "front": "worry!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lek!",
      "front": "play! [unstructured] (e.g. with a friend, animal)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "låt!",
      "front": "let/allow!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "var!",
      "front": "be!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "titta!",
      "front": "look!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag ska betala",
      "front": "I will pay.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vi ska låta henne bestämma",
      "front": "We will let her decide.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "han ska dricka en kaffe till",
      "front": "He will drink another coffee.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag ska bjuda honom på lunch",
      "front": "I will offer him lunch.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "han vill boka en resa",
      "front": "He wants to book a trip.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag ska vila nu",
      "front": "I will rest now.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ska du sluta arbeta",
      "front": "Will you stop working?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag ska leta under sängen",
      "front": "I will look under the bed.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag ska följa dig hem",
      "front": "I will follow you home.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "var ska du hänga nycklarna",
      "front": "Where are you going to hang the keys?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vem ska undervisa i tyska",
      "front": "Who will teach German?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag ska skynda mig",
      "front": "I will hurry!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vi ska gifta oss",
      "front": "We are going to get married!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag tror att det kommer att regna",
      "front": "I think that it is going to rain.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "studenterna kommer att uppnå målet",
      "front": "The students are going to achieve the goal.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "han kommer att tappa paraplyet",
      "front": "He is going to drop the umbrella.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hans fru kommer hem i morgon bitti",
      "front": "His wife is coming home tomorrow morning.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "du kommer att glömma nycklarna",
      "front": "You are going to forget the keys!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det kommer inte att hända",
      "front": "It is not going to happen!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det kommer att ordna sig",
      "front": "It is going to work out.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det kommer inte att fungera",
      "front": "It is not going to work.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ingen kommer att sakna dig",
      "front": "No one is going to miss you.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det kommer inte att påverka oss",
      "front": "It is not going to affect us.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ingenting kommer att hindra henne",
      "front": "Nothing is going to stop her.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vi ska ha fest i övermorgon",
      "front": "We are going to have a party the day after tomorrow.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag hade",
      "front": "I had",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag hade ringt",
      "front": "I had rung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag hade gått",
      "front": "I had gone",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag hade hört",
      "front": "I had heard",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag hade ätit",
      "front": "I had eaten",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag hade hittat",
      "front": "I had found",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag hade kommit",
      "front": "I had come",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag hade gett",
      "front": "I had given",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag hade skrivit",
      "front": "I had written",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag hade tagit",
      "front": "I had taken",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag hade förlorat",
      "front": "I had lost",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag hade skurit",
      "front": "I had cut [i.e. with a knife]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag hade stängt",
      "front": "I had closed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag hade dött",
      "front": "I had died",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag hade försökt",
      "front": "I had tried",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag hade känt",
      "front": "I had known [someone]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag hade känt mig",
      "front": "I had felt [something]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag hade åkt",
      "front": "I had gone/travelled",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag hade öppnat",
      "front": "I had opened",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag hade valt",
      "front": "I had chosen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag hade levt",
      "front": "I had lived [been alive]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag hade upptäckt",
      "front": "I had discovered",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag hade funnits",
      "front": "I had found",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag hade vetat",
      "front": "I had known [something]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag hade glömt",
      "front": "I had forgotten",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vars",
      "front": "whose",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "där",
      "front": "where",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "som",
      "front": "who, that, which",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vad",
      "front": "what",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vilket",
      "front": "which",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att prata",
      "front": "to talk",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att träffa",
      "front": "to meet; to hit a target",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att leva",
      "front": "to live, be alive",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att känna",
      "front": "to know [someone]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att känna sig",
      "front": "to feel [something]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att välja",
      "front": "to choose",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att starta",
      "front": "to begin, to start",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att täcka",
      "front": "to cover",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att öka",
      "front": "to increase",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att bygga",
      "front": "to build",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att lämna",
      "front": "to leave",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att skratta",
      "front": "to laugh",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att flyga",
      "front": "to fly",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att måla",
      "front": "to paint",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att låna",
      "front": "to loan",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att tillämpa",
      "front": "to make use of",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att skada",
      "front": "to hurt, to damage",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att vinna",
      "front": "to win",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att skära",
      "front": "to cut [e.g. knife]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att finna",
      "front": "to exist",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att spara",
      "front": "to save/store for future use",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att tillåta",
      "front": "to allow",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att stoppa",
      "front": "to stuff, to stop",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att förbättra",
      "front": "to improve",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att gråta",
      "front": "to cry",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att förstå",
      "front": "to understand",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att hoppa",
      "front": "to jump",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att sitta",
      "front": "to sit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att stötta",
      "front": "to support [emotionally, physically]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att upprepa",
      "front": "to repeat, to do again",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att repetera",
      "front": "to repeat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att väcka",
      "front": "to wake [someone else]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att utveckla",
      "front": "to develop",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att passa",
      "front": "to fit, to suit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att räkna",
      "front": "to count, to calculate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att stå",
      "front": "to stand",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att dö",
      "front": "to die",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att uppskatta",
      "front": "to appreciate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att tvinga",
      "front": "to force",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att acceptera",
      "front": "to accept",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att bära",
      "front": "to carry",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att undvika",
      "front": "to avoid",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att tillverka",
      "front": "to produce",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att definiera",
      "front": "to define",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att respektera",
      "front": "to respect",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att ställa",
      "front": "to set, to put",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att innehålla",
      "front": "to contain",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att möta",
      "front": "to meet",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att slå",
      "front": "to hit, to strike; to beat [win]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att diskutera",
      "front": "to discuss",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att avsluta",
      "front": "to close, to cancel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att lägga",
      "front": "to lay, to put",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att fylla",
      "front": "to fill, to reach an age",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att blanda",
      "front": "to mix",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att torka",
      "front": "to dry",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att försvinna",
      "front": "to disappear",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att förlora",
      "front": "to lose",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att importera",
      "front": "to import",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att kyssa",
      "front": "to kiss [passionately]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att varna",
      "front": "to warn",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att byta",
      "front": "to switch, to exchange",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att presentera",
      "front": "to present, to introduce",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att förutsätta",
      "front": "to presume/assume, to require",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att flytta",
      "front": "to move",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att lida",
      "front": "to suffer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att förbereda",
      "front": "to prepare",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att hata",
      "front": "to hate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att hämta",
      "front": "to fetch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att förklara",
      "front": "to explain",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att analysera",
      "front": "to analyse",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att bada",
      "front": "to bathe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att älska",
      "front": "to love",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en blomma",
      "front": "a flower",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett träd",
      "front": "a tree",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett hav",
      "front": "a sea, ocean",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett gräs",
      "front": "(a) grass",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en himmel",
      "front": "a sky",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en måne",
      "front": "a moon",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en sol",
      "front": "a sun",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) is",
      "front": "ice",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en värld",
      "front": "a world",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en stjärna",
      "front": "a star",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en eld",
      "front": "a fire",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) luft",
      "front": "(an) air",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en skärgård",
      "front": "an archipelago",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett regn",
      "front": "(a) rain",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en vulkan",
      "front": "a volcano",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en miljö",
      "front": "an environment",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett berg",
      "front": "a mountain",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett fjäll",
      "front": "a mountain",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(ett) väder",
      "front": "(a) weather",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) natur",
      "front": "(a) nature",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en flod",
      "front": "a river",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(ett) trä",
      "front": "(a) wood",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en äng",
      "front": "a meadow",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en våg",
      "front": "a wave, a scale [physical]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en planet",
      "front": "a planet",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en sten",
      "front": "a stone",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en gran",
      "front": "a spruce",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett barr",
      "front": "a needle (of a tree)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett löv",
      "front": "a leaf",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en å",
      "front": "a small river, a creek/stream",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en jord",
      "front": "(a) soil, (an) earth",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att växa",
      "front": "to grow",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett klimat",
      "front": "a climate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett universum",
      "front": "a universe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en rök",
      "front": "a smoke",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett landskap",
      "front": "a landscape",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ros",
      "front": "a {rose}",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det blåser",
      "front": "it blows",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en vind",
      "front": "a wind",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett moln",
      "front": "a cloud",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) sand",
      "front": "(a) sand",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(ett) damm",
      "front": "(a) dust",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en växt",
      "front": "a plant",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en gas",
      "front": "a gas",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett material",
      "front": "a material",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "det snöar",
      "front": "it snows",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) snö",
      "front": "(a) snow",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en metall",
      "front": "a metal",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en blixt",
      "front": "a bolt of lightning",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) åska",
      "front": "(a) thunder",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en rymd",
      "front": "a space",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(ett) norrsken",
      "front": "(a) northern lights",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett vattenfall",
      "front": "a waterfall",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en regnbåg",
      "front": "a rainbow",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) frost",
      "front": "(a) frost",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag sitter och läser",
      "front": "I am reading, I sit and read",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag står och pratar",
      "front": "I am talking, I stand and talk",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag ligger och sover",
      "front": "I am sleeping, I lay and sleep",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jag håller på med att studera",
      "front": "I am studying, I am in the process of studying, I am currently occupying myself with studying",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mjuk",
      "front": "soft",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hård",
      "front": "hard, rigid, inflexible",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lagom",
      "front": "just right, not too little and not too much",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "död",
      "front": "dead",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jobbig",
      "front": "tiresome, hard work",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "farlig",
      "front": "dangerous",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ljus",
      "front": "light (brightness)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "intresserad",
      "front": "interested",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "smart",
      "front": "smart",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sönder",
      "front": "broken, torn, in pieces",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "torr",
      "front": "dry",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mörk",
      "front": "dark",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hög",
      "front": "tall, high",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dum",
      "front": "stupid",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "rak",
      "front": "straight",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "blyg",
      "front": "shy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "gift",
      "front": "married",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "självklar",
      "front": "of course, obviously",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "enda",
      "front": "only",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "annorlunda",
      "front": "different, peculiar",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "illa",
      "front": "bad, poorly, unwell",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tyst",
      "front": "quiet",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vaken",
      "front": "awake",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "blöt",
      "front": "wet",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tung",
      "front": "heavy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tidig",
      "front": "early",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ju A desto B",
      "front": "the A the B [e.g. the more the better]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "värre",
      "front": "worse [when inherently bad e.g. disease]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "värst",
      "front": "worst [when inherently bad e.g. disease]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tjock",
      "front": "thick, fat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "smal",
      "front": "thin, slim",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "flest",
      "front": "the most, the largest number of",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "upptagen",
      "front": "busy, taken, occupied",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "annars",
      "front": "otherwise",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "även",
      "front": "... too/as well [also]; even [not comparison!]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Även du!",
      "front": "You too!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Även en expert kan ta/ha fel.",
      "front": "Even an expert can be wrong.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Även om ...",
      "front": "Even if/though, although",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "i stället (för)",
      "front": "instead",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "alls",
      "front": "at all",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "gärna",
      "front": "gladly, (would) like/love to",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nog",
      "front": "probably; enough",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dessutom",
      "front": "moreover, further more, in addition",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "alltså",
      "front": "thus, hence, therefore",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "däremot",
      "front": "however, on the other hand",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "plötsligt",
      "front": "suddenly",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "helst",
      "front": "(would) rather/prefer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hittills",
      "front": "thus far, up until now",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "allra",
      "front": "very, of all",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "väl",
      "front": "well",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fort",
      "front": "fast, quickly",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ständigt",
      "front": "always, constantly, all the time",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "knappast",
      "front": "hardly, scarcely",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "någonsin",
      "front": "ever",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "igenom",
      "front": "through",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "samtidigt",
      "front": "simultaneously, at the same time",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "genast",
      "front": "immediately, at once",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "drygt",
      "front": "just over",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Nu får det vara nog!",
      "front": "Enough is enough!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Min son ställer ständigt nya frågor.",
      "front": "My son is constantly asking new questions.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en fördel",
      "front": "an advantage, a benefit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en nackdel",
      "front": "a disadvantage, a drawback",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) respekt",
      "front": "(a) respect",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en situation",
      "front": "a situation",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en effektivitet",
      "front": "an efficiency",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en teori",
      "front": "a theory",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) uppmärksamhet",
      "front": "(an) attention",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett misslyckande",
      "front": "a failure",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett intresse",
      "front": "an interest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en sanning",
      "front": "a truth",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en framtid",
      "front": "a future",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett projekt",
      "front": "a project",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tillåtelse",
      "front": "a permission",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en hänsyn",
      "front": "(a) consideration",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att ta hänsyn till",
      "front": "to consider",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en signal",
      "front": "a signal",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en verklighet",
      "front": "a reality",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett ursprung",
      "front": "an origin",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en skada",
      "front": "a wound, an injury, a damage",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en hemlighet",
      "front": "a secret",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en brist",
      "front": "a flaw, a shortcoming",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en upplevelse",
      "front": "an experience [experienced]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en utgång",
      "front": "an exit [pedestrian]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett försök",
      "front": "a try, an attempt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett beteende",
      "front": "a behaviour",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett undantag",
      "front": "an exception",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en erfarenhet",
      "front": "an experience [gained]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en symbol",
      "front": "a symbol",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en styrka",
      "front": "a strength",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en cirkel",
      "front": "a circle",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett läge",
      "front": "a situation, a position",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en form",
      "front": "a form, a shape",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en humor",
      "front": "a humour [sense]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en relation",
      "front": "a relation",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en rädsla",
      "front": "a fear, a dread",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett tillstånd",
      "front": "a permit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en konversation",
      "front": "a conversation",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett nöje",
      "front": "a joy, a pleasure",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) trovärdighet",
      "front": "(a) reliability, trustworthiness",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tradition",
      "front": "a tradition",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en konsekvens",
      "front": "a consequence",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en stöld",
      "front": "a theft",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en överraskning",
      "front": "a surprise",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tjänst",
      "front": "a service; a favour; a duty",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en trend",
      "front": "a trend",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en fras",
      "front": "a phrase",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en attityd",
      "front": "an attitude",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett mord",
      "front": "a murder",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett misstag",
      "front": "a mistake",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en personlighet",
      "front": "a personality, a character",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en glädje",
      "front": "a joy, a happiness",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ära",
      "front": "an honour",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en skugga",
      "front": "a shadow",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett minne",
      "front": "a memory, a recollection",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ingång",
      "front": "an entrance (pedestrians)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en fara",
      "front": "a danger",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Hur är läget?",
      "front": "How\u0027s it going?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett steg",
      "front": "a step",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att spela",
      "front": "to play [structured] (e.g. music, game, instrument)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett mål",
      "front": "a goal, an objective",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att slå",
      "front": "to beat (win)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en poäng",
      "front": "a point (score)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett spel",
      "front": "a game",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en fotboll",
      "front": "a football",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en basket",
      "front": "a basketball",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tränare",
      "front": "a trainer, a coach",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en racket",
      "front": "a racket",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en volleyboll",
      "front": "a volleyball",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att sparka",
      "front": "to kick",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en plan",
      "front": "a field",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) tennis",
      "front": "a tennis",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en match",
      "front": "a match, a game",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett gym",
      "front": "a gym",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en turnering",
      "front": "a tournament",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en idrott",
      "front": "a sport [physical]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) innebandy",
      "front": "(a) floorball",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en golf",
      "front": "(a) golf",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att kasta",
      "front": "to cast, to throw",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en skida",
      "front": "a ski",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att skida",
      "front": "to ski",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en klubba",
      "front": "a stick, a club",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) ishockey",
      "front": "(an) icehockey",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett lopp",
      "front": "a run, a race, a track",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att klara av",
      "front": "to manage, to tackle",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att göra mål",
      "front": "to score (a goal)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att slå sönder",
      "front": "to break",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Klara. Färdiga. Kör!",
      "front": "Ready. Set. Go!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en fotbollsplan",
      "front": "a football field/pitch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "upp",
      "front": "up [direction]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "uppe",
      "front": "up [location]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "däruppe",
      "front": "up there [location]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "häruppe",
      "front": "up here [location]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ner",
      "front": "down [direction]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nere",
      "front": "down [location]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "härnere",
      "front": "down here [location]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "därnere",
      "front": "down there [location]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fram",
      "front": "forward, in front",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "framme",
      "front": "there, at the goal",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att komma fram",
      "front": "to arrive",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att vara framme",
      "front": "to be there",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hem",
      "front": "home [direction]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hemma",
      "front": "(at) home [location]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hemifrån",
      "front": "away from home [direction]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "förbi",
      "front": "past",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "in",
      "front": "in [direction]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "inne",
      "front": "in [location], inside",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "härinne",
      "front": "in here [location]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "därinne",
      "front": "in there [location]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ut",
      "front": "out [direction]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ute",
      "front": "out [location], outside",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "därute",
      "front": "out there [location]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "härute",
      "front": "out here [location]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att klättra",
      "front": "to climb",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att rinna",
      "front": "to run, to flow",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "uppför",
      "front": "up, upward, upphill",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nedför",
      "front": "down, downward, downhill",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ur",
      "front": "of/from [direction]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ut ur",
      "front": "out of/from",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "här",
      "front": "here [location]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hit",
      "front": "here [direction]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "där",
      "front": "there [location]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dit",
      "front": "there [direction]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "härifrån",
      "front": "away from here [direction]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "därifrån",
      "front": "away from there [direction]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ihop",
      "front": "together",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att sitta ihop",
      "front": "to stick together",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att sätta ihop",
      "front": "to assemble, to put together",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att sätta sig",
      "front": "to sit one\u0027s self down",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "inom",
      "front": "within, inside",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "omkring",
      "front": "around, about",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en mitt",
      "front": "a middle",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett håll",
      "front": "a direction, a distance",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "därunder",
      "front": "under there [location]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "härunder",
      "front": "under here [location]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "uppåt",
      "front": "up towards",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nedåt",
      "front": "down towards",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kamera",
      "front": "a camera",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en musik",
      "front": "(a) music",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en fiol",
      "front": "a violin, a fiddle",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en film",
      "front": "a film, a movie",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en flöjt",
      "front": "a flute",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en saga",
      "front": "a story, a fairytale",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att handla om",
      "front": "to be about",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett kort",
      "front": "a photo, a picture; a card",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en konst",
      "front": "(an) art",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett ljud",
      "front": "a sound",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en gitarr",
      "front": "a guitar",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en stil",
      "front": "a style",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett piano",
      "front": "a piano",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en sång",
      "front": "a song",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en fotografi",
      "front": "(a) photography",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en hjälte",
      "front": "a hero",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en hjältinna",
      "front": "a heroine",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en dans",
      "front": "a dance",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en teater",
      "front": "a theatre",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) litteratur",
      "front": "(a) literature",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en konstnär",
      "front": "an artist",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett mode",
      "front": "a fashion",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en teckning",
      "front": "a drawing",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett instrument",
      "front": "an instrument",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en konsert",
      "front": "a concert",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tavla",
      "front": "a painting",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en publik",
      "front": "an audience",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en poesi",
      "front": "(a) poetry",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en invigning",
      "front": "an opening, an inauguration",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tävling",
      "front": "a contest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en novell",
      "front": "a short story, a novella",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en trumma",
      "front": "a drum",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att dansa",
      "front": "to dance",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "rund",
      "front": "round",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en scen",
      "front": "a scene, a stage",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en boksamling",
      "front": "a book collection",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en frimärkssamling",
      "front": "a stamp collection",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att skapa",
      "front": "to create",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett band",
      "front": "a band",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en samling",
      "front": "a collection",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en konstsamling",
      "front": "an art collection",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en hand",
      "front": "a hand",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) vård",
      "front": "(a) care",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sjuk",
      "front": "sick",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett öga",
      "front": "an eye",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett huvud",
      "front": "a head",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett hjärta",
      "front": "a heart",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kropp",
      "front": "a body",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en hälsa",
      "front": "(a) health",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett ansikte",
      "front": "a face",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en medicin",
      "front": "a medicine",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en behandling",
      "front": "a treatment",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett hår",
      "front": "a hair",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett nödfall",
      "front": "an emergency",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en glasögon",
      "front": "(a pair of) glasses",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en cancer",
      "front": "a cancer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ambulans",
      "front": "an ambulance",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en patient",
      "front": "a patient",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett sjukhus",
      "front": "a hospital",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en sjukdom",
      "front": "a disease, an illness",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(ett) blod",
      "front": "(a) blood",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en hud",
      "front": "(a) skin",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en operation",
      "front": "an operation, a surgery",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en syn",
      "front": "(a) sight; a vision",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett virus",
      "front": "a virus",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en fot",
      "front": "a foot",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att blöda",
      "front": "to bleed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en smärta",
      "front": "a pain, an ache",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en blick",
      "front": "a gaze, a glance",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en mun",
      "front": "a mouth",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en olycka",
      "front": "an accident",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en hjärna",
      "front": "a brain",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en arm",
      "front": "an arm",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett sår",
      "front": "a sore, a wound",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett ben",
      "front": "a leg",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en hals",
      "front": "a neck, a throat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en bilolycka",
      "front": "a car accident",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tunga",
      "front": "a tongue",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett öra",
      "front": "an ear",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett bröst",
      "front": "a chest, a breast",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att blunda",
      "front": "to close the eyes",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett finger",
      "front": "a finger",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tand",
      "front": "a tooth",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tänder",
      "front": "teeth",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att hosta",
      "front": "to cough",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tå",
      "front": "a toe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en läpp",
      "front": "a lip",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en näsa",
      "front": "a nose",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en rygg",
      "front": "a back",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en sjuksköterska",
      "front": "a nurse",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att nysa",
      "front": "to sneeze",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "gravid",
      "front": "pregnant",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en mage",
      "front": "a stomach",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kind",
      "front": "a cheek",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att andas",
      "front": "to breathe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att svettas",
      "front": "to sweat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en nagel",
      "front": "a nail",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fötter",
      "front": "feet",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "händer",
      "front": "hands",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att vara förkyld",
      "front": "to have a cold",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en statsminister",
      "front": "a prime minister",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en regering",
      "front": "a government",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) säkerhet",
      "front": "(a) safety, security",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en makt",
      "front": "a power",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en politiker",
      "front": "a politician",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en lag",
      "front": "a law",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en krig",
      "front": "a war",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett samhälle",
      "front": "a society",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en president",
      "front": "a president",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett parti",
      "front": "a political party, a side in an argument, a game of e.g. chess",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att rösta",
      "front": "to vote",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en strategi",
      "front": "a strategy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett råd",
      "front": "(a piece of) advice, (a) counsel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett sammanträde",
      "front": "a meeting, a session, an assembly",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en fred",
      "front": "a peace [national, international]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en frihet",
      "front": "(a) freedom",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tjuv",
      "front": "a thief",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att stjäla",
      "front": "to steal",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) politik",
      "front": "(a) politics",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att kräva",
      "front": "to demand",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett våld",
      "front": "a violence",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en armé",
      "front": "an army",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att begå",
      "front": "to commit, to perform",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett brott",
      "front": "a crime, a fracture",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett mord",
      "front": "a murder",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ordförande",
      "front": "a chairmain, a chairwoman",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ledare",
      "front": "a leader",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett hot",
      "front": "a threat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att fatta",
      "front": "to make [a decision]; to grasp, understand",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att hålla tal",
      "front": "to give a speech",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en demokrati",
      "front": "a democracy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett tal",
      "front": "a speech",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ledamot",
      "front": "a member (board or committee)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(ett) sameting",
      "front": "(a) sami parliament",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en flotta",
      "front": "a navy, a fleet",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en konflikt",
      "front": "a conflict, an argument",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kris",
      "front": "a crisis",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kandidat",
      "front": "a candidate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en riksdag",
      "front": "a parliament",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en riksdagsledamot",
      "front": "a member of parliament",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att skjuta",
      "front": "to shoot",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en pistol",
      "front": "a pistol, a gun",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en borgmästare",
      "front": "a mayor",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en strejk",
      "front": "a strike",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att äga",
      "front": "to own",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en domstol",
      "front": "a court",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "i hjäl",
      "front": "to death",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att döda",
      "front": "to kill",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett gevär",
      "front": "a rifle",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett vapen",
      "front": "a weapon",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "överens",
      "front": "in agreement",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ägare",
      "front": "an owner",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en invånare",
      "front": "an inhabitant",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en plan",
      "front": "a plan",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att söka",
      "front": "to search",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en text",
      "front": "(a) text",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en press",
      "front": "a press",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kommentar",
      "front": "a comment",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett nätverk",
      "front": "a network",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en information",
      "front": "(a piece of) information",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en sökning",
      "front": "a search",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett språk",
      "front": "a language",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett program",
      "front": "a program",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kanal",
      "front": "a channel, a canal",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en nyhet",
      "front": "(a) news",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett vykort",
      "front": "a postcard",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett meddelande",
      "front": "a message",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en berättelse",
      "front": "a story, a narrative",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att ladda",
      "front": "to load, to charge",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att ladda ner",
      "front": "to download",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att ladda upp",
      "front": "to upload",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(ett) internet",
      "front": "(an) internet",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kommunikation",
      "front": "(a) communication",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett frimärke",
      "front": "a stamp",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tillgång",
      "front": "an access",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(ett) nät",
      "front": "(a) network, (the) web",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en journalist",
      "front": "a journalist",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en underskrift",
      "front": "a signature",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en läsare",
      "front": "a reader",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett lösenord",
      "front": "a password",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att intervjua",
      "front": "to interview",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett användarnamn",
      "front": "a username",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att gälla",
      "front": "to concern, to be about",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en mening",
      "front": "a sentence, a meaning",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en bokstav",
      "front": "a letter [alphabet]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "uppäten",
      "front": "eaten",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "överraskad",
      "front": "surprised",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "inbjuden",
      "front": "invited",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "stängd",
      "front": "closed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "stulen",
      "front": "stolen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "irriterad",
      "front": "irritated",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "misslyckad",
      "front": "failed, like a failure",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "öppnade",
      "front": "opened",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "döende",
      "front": "dying",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "irriterande",
      "front": "irritating, annoying",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "överraskande",
      "front": "surprising",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "simmande",
      "front": "swimming",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sovande",
      "front": "sleeping",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "gående",
      "front": "walking",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lekande",
      "front": "playing [unstructured]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "springande",
      "front": "running",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hängande",
      "front": "hanging",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "blivande",
      "front": "future",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "flygande",
      "front": "flying",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sittande",
      "front": "sitting",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fungerande",
      "front": "functioning",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "talande",
      "front": "telling, speaking",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "givande",
      "front": "rewarding, giving",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "levande",
      "front": "living",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "passande",
      "front": "suitable, fitting",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kommande",
      "front": "coming, future",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "liggande",
      "front": "laying",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Pappa kommer att ha tagit dina pengar.",
      "front": "Dad will have taken your money.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Efter den här kursen kommer du att ha lärt dig många ord.",
      "front": "After this course you will have learnt many words.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "De kommer att ha hittat henne nästa vecka.",
      "front": "They will have found her next week.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Han kommer att ha ringt.",
      "front": "He will have rung.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Min fru kommer att ha bestämt sig i morgon.",
      "front": "My wife will have decided tomorrow.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Skolan kommer att ha skickat all information.",
      "front": "The School will have sent all information.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Hon kommer att ha fått en leksak i morgon.",
      "front": "She will have gotten a toy tomorrow.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "På fredag kommer jag redan att ha lärt mig mycket.",
      "front": "On Friday I will already have learnt a lot.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Kommer hon att ha fått den på torsdag?",
      "front": "Will she have received it on Thursday?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Kommer de att ha skickat vykortet i morgon?",
      "front": "Will they have sent the postcard tomorrow?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) el",
      "front": "(an) electricity",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en analys",
      "front": "an analysis",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en linje",
      "front": "a line",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en artikel",
      "front": "an article",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en detalj",
      "front": "a detail",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en storlek",
      "front": "a size",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en teknologi",
      "front": "a technology",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en forskning",
      "front": "(a piece of) research",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en längd",
      "front": "a length, a height",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en bredd",
      "front": "a width",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en vikt",
      "front": "a weight",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en energi",
      "front": "an energy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en metod",
      "front": "a method",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en vetenskap",
      "front": "a science",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett eluttag",
      "front": "a power outlet",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att höja",
      "front": "to raise",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en volym",
      "front": "a volume",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att sänka",
      "front": "to lower, to reduce",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en hastighet",
      "front": "a speed, a velocity",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en skala",
      "front": "a scale [abstract]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett avstånd",
      "front": "a distance",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en yta",
      "front": "a surface",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en definition",
      "front": "a definition",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ytlig",
      "front": "superficial",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ytligt",
      "front": "superficially",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en våg",
      "front": "a wave, a scale [physical]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att väga",
      "front": "to weigh",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en temperatur",
      "front": "a temperature",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett kilo",
      "front": "a kilogram",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett laboratorium",
      "front": "a laboratory",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en massa",
      "front": "a mass; a load of",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en filosofi",
      "front": "a philosophy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en teknik",
      "front": "a technique",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en höjd",
      "front": "a height",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en uppgift",
      "front": "a task/exercise; (a piece of) information",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) fysik",
      "front": "(a) physics",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett mått",
      "front": "a measurement",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att mätta",
      "front": "to fill, to feed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett nobelpris",
      "front": "a nobel prize",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) kemi",
      "front": "(a) chemistry",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en upptäckt",
      "front": "a discovery",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en formel",
      "front": "a formula",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en prick",
      "front": "a dot, a spot",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett begrepp",
      "front": "a concept",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att mäta",
      "front": "to measure",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) geografi",
      "front": "(a) geography",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en forskare",
      "front": "a scientist",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att dra",
      "front": "to drag, to draw (a conclusion)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en alkohol",
      "front": "an alcohol",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att forska",
      "front": "to research",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en akademi",
      "front": "an academy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att upptäcka",
      "front": "to discover",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en slutsats",
      "front": "a conclusion",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mätt",
      "front": "full, satisified (from eating)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Vad skulle du svara om han frågade?",
      "front": "What/How would you answer if he asked?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Skulle han äta surströmming?",
      "front": "Would he eat fermented herring?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Om jag hade pengar skulle jag köpa nya kläder.",
      "front": "If I had money I would buy new clothes.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag skulle ge dig pengar om jag hade några.",
      "front": "I would give you money if I had any.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Vad skulle du vilja ha?",
      "front": "What would you like (to have)?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag skulle vilja träffa henne igen.",
      "front": "I would like to meet her again.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Skulle du bli ledsen om hon inte kommer?",
      "front": "Would you be sad if she did not come?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag skulle ha gått",
      "front": "I would have gone.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Vad skulle du ha ändrat?",
      "front": "What would you have changed?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Hon skulle ha skrivit en längre bok.",
      "front": "She would have written a longer book.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Hon skulle ha varit där.",
      "front": "She would have been there.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Vad skulle du ha haft i väskan?",
      "front": "What would you have had in the bag?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Han skulle ha skrivit.",
      "front": "He would have written.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Vi skulle ha varit glada.",
      "front": "We would have been happy.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag skulle inte ha ändrat någonting.",
      "front": "I would have not changed anything.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Varför skulle du ha ändrat det?",
      "front": "Why would you have changed it?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Skulle du ha gått tillbaka?",
      "front": "Would you have gone back?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Du skulle ha ringt honom.",
      "front": "You would have rung him.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Vad vore jag utan dig?",
      "front": "What would I be without you?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Vad skulle du göra om du var jag?",
      "front": "What would you do if you were me?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Skulle jag kunna få ett glas vatten.",
      "front": "Would I be able to/Could I get a glass of water?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Han skulle ha läst boken om hon hade skrivit den.",
      "front": "He would have read the book if she had have written it.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag skulle ha gett dig allt jag har.",
      "front": "I would have given you everything I have.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tomte",
      "front": "a gnome",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett troll",
      "front": "a troll",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en jultom",
      "front": "(a) santa claus",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en gud",
      "front": "a god",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en gudinna",
      "front": "a goddess",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "andlig",
      "front": "spiritual",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett spöke",
      "front": "a ghost",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en religion",
      "front": "a religion",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tro",
      "front": "a faith, a belief",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ängel",
      "front": "an angel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ande",
      "front": "a ghost, a spirit, a genie",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en moské",
      "front": "a mosque",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en bön",
      "front": "a prayer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en nåd",
      "front": "a mercy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "osynlig",
      "front": "invisible",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en själ",
      "front": "a soul",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "helig",
      "front": "holy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett öde",
      "front": "a destiny, a fate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en död",
      "front": "a death",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en påve",
      "front": "a pope",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en grav",
      "front": "a grave",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en trollkarl",
      "front": "a wizard",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en häxa",
      "front": "a witch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Antalet kan höjas.",
      "front": "The number can be raised/increased.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Att älska och älskas.",
      "front": "To love and be loved.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Huset måste flyttas.",
      "front": "The house must be moved.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Systemet kan kritiseras på många sätt.",
      "front": "The system can be criticised in many ways.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Filmen sågs av en mycket stor publik.",
      "front": "The film was seen by a very large audience.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Denna typ av skor bars av bönder.",
      "front": "This type of shoe is worn by farmers.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Boken ska tryckas i Polen.",
      "front": "The book will be printed in Poland.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Projektet stoppades.",
      "front": "The projected was stopped.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Teorin kritiserades i en bok.",
      "front": "The theory was criticised in a book.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Den nya kyrkan byggdes förra året.",
      "front": "The new church was built last year.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Boken trycktes förra året.",
      "front": "The book was printed last year.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Planerna måste stoppas.",
      "front": "The plans must be stopped.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Vi blev förhörda av polisen.",
      "front": "We were interrogated by the police.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Förslaget blev stoppat.",
      "front": "The proposal/suggestion was stopped.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Kakan är bakad av min man.",
      "front": "The cake was baked by my husband.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Vi blev rånade av några killar.",
      "front": "We were robbed by some guys.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Han blev illa behandlad i fängelset.",
      "front": "He was mistreated in prison.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Hunden blev överkörd.",
      "front": "The dog got run over.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag blev stoppad av polisen.",
      "front": "I got stopped by the police.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Brödet är bakat i går.",
      "front": "The bread was baked yesterday.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Det var jobbigt att bli förhörd.",
      "front": "It was hard to be interrogated.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Politikern blev rånad av två unga kvinnor.",
      "front": "The politician was robbed by two young women.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Telefonen är tillverkad i Finland.",
      "front": "The telephone is produced in Finland.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Skåpet är tillverkat i Göteborg.",
      "front": "The cupboard is produced in Gothenburg.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Leksakerna är tillverkade av oss.",
      "front": "The toys are produced by us.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Är du skadad?",
      "front": "Are you hurt/damaged?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Boken är tryckt i Kina.",
      "front": "The book is printed in China.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Huset är ritat av en finsk arkitekt.",
      "front": "The house was drawn by a Finnish architect.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Du är älskad av alla.",
      "front": "You are loved by everyone/all.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Tidningarna är tryckta på billigt papper.",
      "front": "The newspapers are printed on cheap paper.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Teckningen är ritad av en konstnär.",
      "front": "The drawing is by an artist.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Flera spelare är skadade.",
      "front": "Several players are hurt/damaged.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Vi skulle börja med att spela fotboll, men han hade glömt bollen hemma.",
      "front": "We were going to start playing football but he had forgotten the ball at home.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag visste inte att de skulle komma.",
      "front": "I did not know that they were going to come.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag hoppades att du skulle komma.",
      "front": "I was hoping (that) you would come.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Hon gick tidigare, eftersom hon skulle träffa sin syster.",
      "front": "She went earlier since/because she was going to meet her sister.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "I går var jag nervös eftersom jag skulle träffa kungen.",
      "front": "Yesterday I was nervous since/because I was going to meet the king.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Han såg ut som om han skulle börja gråta.",
      "front": "He looked as if/though he was going to start crying.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Hon skulle komma efter honom.",
      "front": "She was going to come after him.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "De skulle åka till Frankrike på semester.",
      "front": "They were going to go to France on vacation/holiday.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en styrelse",
      "front": "a council, a board",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett företag",
      "front": "a company",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ränta",
      "front": "an interest (rate)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en procent",
      "front": "a percent",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en skuld",
      "front": "a debt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en skatt",
      "front": "a tax, a treasure",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en försäkring",
      "front": "(an) insurance",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att gå ut",
      "front": "to expire",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ekonomi",
      "front": "an economy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en industri",
      "front": "an industry",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en risk",
      "front": "a risk",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett guld",
      "front": "(a) gold",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en investering",
      "front": "an investment",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett erbjudande",
      "front": "an offer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en förmögenhet",
      "front": "a fortune",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett varumärke",
      "front": "a brand",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en konkurrens",
      "front": "(a) competition",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en produkt",
      "front": "a product",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett kreditkort",
      "front": "a credit card",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) handel",
      "front": "(a) trade, commerce",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en rea",
      "front": "a sale",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att ta slut",
      "front": "to run out, come to an end",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en budget",
      "front": "a budget",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en handelspartner",
      "front": "a trade partner",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en organisation",
      "front": "an organisation",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att befordra",
      "front": "to promote",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett avtal",
      "front": "a deal, an agreement",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kostnad",
      "front": "a cost",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en valuta",
      "front": "a currency",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en reklam",
      "front": "an advert",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en öre",
      "front": "a cent, an ore, an öre",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett möte",
      "front": "a meeting",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett pris",
      "front": "a price",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "global",
      "front": "global",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett kontrakt",
      "front": "a contract",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kund",
      "front": "a customer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att minska",
      "front": "to decrease",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en vinst",
      "front": "a profit, a gain",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en förlust",
      "front": "a loss",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en check",
      "front": "a cheque, a check",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kontant",
      "front": "in cash",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en konkurs",
      "front": "a bankruptcy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en aktie",
      "front": "a share",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en lön",
      "front": "a wage, a salary",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "på vinst och förlust",
      "front": "on speculation, at a venture",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en bilindustri",
      "front": "a car industry",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en födelsedag",
      "front": "a birthday",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett kalas",
      "front": "a party (esp. children\u0027s]; a feast",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en present",
      "front": "a gift, a present",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att fylla år",
      "front": "to have a birthday",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en läsk",
      "front": "a soft drink",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(ett) godis",
      "front": "(a) sweets, (a) candies",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en inbjudan",
      "front": "an invitation",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att fira",
      "front": "to celebrate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en påsk",
      "front": "an easter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Skål!",
      "front": "Cheers!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en fyrverkeri",
      "front": "a firework",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kräftskiva",
      "front": "a crayfish party",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en nationaldag",
      "front": "a national day",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en helgdag",
      "front": "a (public) holiday",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Grattis!",
      "front": "Congratulations!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) champagne",
      "front": "(a) champagne",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett nyår",
      "front": "(a) New Year\u0027s Eve",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett smörgåsbord",
      "front": "a smorgosbord, a sandwich table",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nu för tiden",
      "front": "nowadays",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "då och då",
      "front": "now and again",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "i själva verket",
      "front": "in fact/actuality",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vice versa",
      "front": "vice versa",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "på sista tiden",
      "front": "recently",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "på det hela taget",
      "front": "on the whole",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "i så fall",
      "front": "in that case, if so",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "framför allt",
      "front": "above all",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "inte det minsta",
      "front": "not in the least/slightest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "varje gång",
      "front": "every time",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lika bra som",
      "front": "as good/well as",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "så att säga",
      "front": "so to speak, as it were",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "upp och ner",
      "front": "upside down",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "i alla fall",
      "front": "even so, all the same, in any case",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "på grund av",
      "front": "due to, on grounds of",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "gång på gång",
      "front": "repeatedly, time and time again",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "helt och hållet",
      "front": "completely, entirely",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "i första taget",
      "front": "in a hurry",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "frisk",
      "front": "healthy; fresh",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "klok",
      "front": "wise, intelligent",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lugn",
      "front": "calm, tranquil",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "trygg",
      "front": "safe, secure, reliable",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tuff",
      "front": "tough, trendy [colloquial]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "manlig",
      "front": "manly",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kvinnlig",
      "front": "womanly",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "rimlig",
      "front": "reasonable, sensible, plausible",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ärlig",
      "front": "honest, straightforward, honourable, sincere",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "härlig",
      "front": "sweet, lovely, very pleasant",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kraftig",
      "front": "powerful, strong, substantial, heavy, sturdy, robust",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "märklig",
      "front": "remarkable",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fullständig",
      "front": "complete, entire",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tveksam",
      "front": "hesitant, doubtful, uncertain",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "oskyldig",
      "front": "innocent, guiltless, harmless",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "stolt",
      "front": "proud, noble, glorious",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sakta",
      "front": "slow, gentle, soft",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "spännande",
      "front": "exciting",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "främmande",
      "front": "strange, unknown, unfamiliar, foreign",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lidande",
      "front": "suffering",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "förvånad",
      "front": "amazed, astounded, astonished",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "begränsad",
      "front": "limited, restricted, narrow",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ekonomisk",
      "front": "economic, economical",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nuvarande",
      "front": "present, relating to now",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ytterligare",
      "front": "additional",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "skyldig",
      "front": "guilty, obliged, liable",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hemlig",
      "front": "secret",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "våldsam",
      "front": "violent",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "övrig",
      "front": "other, remaining",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tillfällig",
      "front": "occasional, accidental, incidental, temporary, momentary",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "skriftlig",
      "front": "written",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "gemensam",
      "front": "common, joint, mutual",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "frivillig",
      "front": "voluntary, optional",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "facklig",
      "front": "professional, technical, relating to a trade/labour union",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "såsom",
      "front": "[in the same way] as; like",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "varsin",
      "front": "each [on/for their own]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "varannan",
      "front": "every other, alternately",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nyss",
      "front": "very recently",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fast",
      "front": "fixed, firmly, steadily",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jämt",
      "front": "always",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "åter",
      "front": "re-, once again, back",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "delvis",
      "front": "partially, in part",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "enbart",
      "front": "solely, exclusively, entirely, merely, simply",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fullständigt",
      "front": "completely, entirely",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "svårt",
      "front": "heavily, severely, seriously, grievously",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "inför",
      "front": "in front of, while having the attention of, in preparation for",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ytterligare",
      "front": "further",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "än så länge",
      "front": "so far, up until now",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ända",
      "front": "as far as, all the way to",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "visserligen",
      "front": "true, certainly, to be sure, indeed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sakta",
      "front": "slowly; gently; softly",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "noga",
      "front": "carefully",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hastigt",
      "front": "hastily",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "utomhus",
      "front": "outside, outdoors",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "inomhus",
      "front": "inside, indoors",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "härtill",
      "front": "to this, in view of this",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "därtill",
      "front": "to that, in view of that",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en juridik",
      "front": "(a) law [the study of]; a legal system",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett anslag",
      "front": "a plot, conspiracy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett vittne",
      "front": "a witness",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en slav",
      "front": "a slave",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en myndighet",
      "front": "an authority",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en utredning",
      "front": "an investigation",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett spår",
      "front": "a track, a mark",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en aning",
      "front": "an idea, a suspicion, a notion",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en jakt",
      "front": "a hunt, a chase, a yacht",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en rättegång",
      "front": "a trial, a case",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en åklagare",
      "front": "a prosecutor",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en fånge",
      "front": "a prisoner, a convict",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en rättighet",
      "front": "a right",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en betalning",
      "front": "a payment, a settlement, compensation",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en skyldighet",
      "front": "a duty, obligation",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en dom",
      "front": "a {doom}; a conviction, judgement, verdict; (a) doomsday",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett straff",
      "front": "a punishment, a penalty, a sentence",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en lögn",
      "front": "a lie",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en trygghet",
      "front": "a safety, a security",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett skydd",
      "front": "a protection, shelter, cover, refuge",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) jämställdhet",
      "front": "(a) gender equality",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en drog",
      "front": "a drug",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en hora",
      "front": "a whore",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett rån",
      "front": "a robbery, a wafer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att ske",
      "front": "to happen, what happens over time",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att synas",
      "front": "to appear, to see, to be visible",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att innebära",
      "front": "to imply, mean, signify",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att föreslå",
      "front": "to suggest, propose",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att stämma",
      "front": "to agree, correspond; to arrange [e.g. meeting]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att anse",
      "front": "to think, consider, regard, be of the opinion",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att pågå",
      "front": "to continue, to be in progress",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att släppa",
      "front": "to let/allow [in]; to release",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att kämpa",
      "front": "to fight, struggle, strive",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att vägra",
      "front": "to refuse",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att bryta",
      "front": "to break; to break (disrepect) a law/rule",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att skaffa",
      "front": "to get, to acquire, to procure",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att behålla",
      "front": "to keep, maintain posession of",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att tillhöra",
      "front": "to belong to",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att bestå",
      "front": "to consist; to persist, prevail",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att skilja",
      "front": "to differ, discern; to separate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att röra",
      "front": "to move, stir; to touch; to confuse",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att rycka",
      "front": "to tug, yank, jerk, pull quickly",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att fundera",
      "front": "to ponder",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att lösa",
      "front": "to solve, to dissolve",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att lova",
      "front": "to promise, to assure",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att luta",
      "front": "to lean, to slope",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att vända",
      "front": "to turn",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att vika",
      "front": "to fold [e.g. clothes]; to fold [give in/up]; to dedicate/set aside time; (refl.) to bend [from laughing]; (refl.) to go to bed [sleep]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att vika ut",
      "front": "to unfold [e.g. map]; to expose oneself",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Jag går och viker mig.",
      "front": "I am going to bed.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Vika åt sidan.",
      "front": "Turn/step/stand aside.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att falla",
      "front": "to fall, drop; to fall over, trip, stumble",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att sköta",
      "front": "to attend, to keep, maintain, to nurse, care for",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett lik",
      "front": "a corpse",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett slag",
      "front": "a hit, stroke, strike, a sort, a moment",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en verksamhet",
      "front": "an activity, a business, enterprise, operation",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en stöd",
      "front": "(a) support",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en skillnad",
      "front": "a difference",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en grund",
      "front": "a ground, land, a foundation, a cause, reason, basis",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett behov",
      "front": "a need, a requirement",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en anledning",
      "front": "a reason; a cause/grounds",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett håll",
      "front": "a stop, a station, a direction, a distance",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en port",
      "front": "an entrance, a gate, a doorway, a portal",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en handling",
      "front": "an act, deed, an action, a storyline, (a) shopping",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett tillfälle",
      "front": "an opportunity, an occasion, an instance",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en takt",
      "front": "a rhythm, a pace",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en källa",
      "front": "a source",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en lokal",
      "front": "a place, locality, premise, a habitat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett villkor",
      "front": "a condition, a precondition",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en orsak",
      "front": "a cause/grounds; a reason",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en chans",
      "front": "a chance, opportunity",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ordning",
      "front": "(an) order; a tidiness",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en herr",
      "front": "a mister, a sir",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett tryck",
      "front": "a pressure, a print",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett ryck",
      "front": "a pull, a yank, a jerk",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett bidrag",
      "front": "a contribution, a subsidy, a social benefit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en förening",
      "front": "an assosciation, union, society, club",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en gemenskap",
      "front": "a community, a fellowship",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en skiva",
      "front": "a slice; a disc; a record [e.g. music]; a social gathering [colloquial]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att råka",
      "front": "to come across, encounter, to happen/chance to",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att drabba",
      "front": "to befall, happen to, fall upon, hit, strike",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att påstå",
      "front": "to say, state, declare, assert, maintain, contend, argue",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att kontrollera",
      "front": "to check (up on), verify, test, inspect",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att erbjuda",
      "front": "to offer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att ange",
      "front": "to state, mention, report, to indicate, mark, note",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att anmäla",
      "front": "to report, to notify",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att behandla",
      "front": "to treat, handle, attend \u003cto\u003e, deal \u003cwith\u003e",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att ingå",
      "front": "to be included",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att styra",
      "front": "to steer, drive, guide, direct",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att bilda",
      "front": "to form, to build, to shape, to educate, to inform",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att samla",
      "front": "to collect, to gather, to organise",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att sprida",
      "front": "to spread, to distribute",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att eka",
      "front": "to echo",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att genomföra",
      "front": "to carry out, realise, to accomplish",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att peka",
      "front": "to point",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att påpeka",
      "front": "to point out",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att hantera",
      "front": "to handle, manage",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att döma",
      "front": "to judge, sentence, condemn",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att tyda",
      "front": "to indicate, point to, to interpret, decipher",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att bedöma",
      "front": "to judge, to form an opinion, to mark, grade, to evaluate, to criticize",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att erkänna",
      "front": "to confess, admit; to recognise, acknowledge",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att tolka",
      "front": "to interpret",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att ägna",
      "front": "to devote, dedicate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att satsa",
      "front": "to stake, venture, invest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att lyfta",
      "front": "to lift",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att riva",
      "front": "to tear, to rip",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en skull",
      "front": "(a) behalf, sake",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en rubrik",
      "front": "a header, a headline",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en herre",
      "front": "a gentleman, a master",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en make",
      "front": "a married man, male spouse",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en maka",
      "front": "a married woman, female spouse",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tolkning",
      "front": "an interpretation",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en motståndare",
      "front": "an opponent",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett bud",
      "front": "a command, order, an offer, bid, a message",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett äktenskap",
      "front": "a marriage",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en oro",
      "front": "an anxiety, concern, worry",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tant",
      "front": "an aunt, an (older) woman",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en gäng",
      "front": "a gang, a team, a group",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en deltagare",
      "front": "a participant",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) kristendom",
      "front": "(a) Christianity",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en besked",
      "front": "(an) information, instructions, a message",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en granne",
      "front": "a neighbour",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en hustru",
      "front": "a wife",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en räkning",
      "front": "an invoice, bill; a counting, calculation",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en anställning",
      "front": "a position, post, an employment",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tjänsteman",
      "front": "a clerk",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en utställning",
      "front": "an exhibition",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en läggning",
      "front": "a disposition, a temperament",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett löfte",
      "front": "a promise",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en lust",
      "front": "a desire, a lust",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kassa",
      "front": "a counter, cash register, a fund, capital",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en avdelning",
      "front": "a department, division",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att godkänna",
      "front": "to approve (of), agree (to)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att förbjuda",
      "front": "to forbid, prohibit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att bete sig",
      "front": "to behave one\u0027s self",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att umgås",
      "front": "to socialise",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att roa",
      "front": "to amuse, to entertain",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att lura",
      "front": "to trick, to fool, to deceive",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att motivera",
      "front": "to motivate, to justify, warrant",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att uppträda",
      "front": "to appear, to act, perform",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att skrämma",
      "front": "to frighten, scare",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att ropa",
      "front": "to shout, call",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att gripa",
      "front": "to catch hold of, seize",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att mörda",
      "front": "to murder",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att skaka",
      "front": "to shake, tremble",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att vandra",
      "front": "to wander, hike",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att skämma",
      "front": "to spoil, ruin, to dishonour",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att rymma",
      "front": "to escape, run away, to accomodate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att gömma",
      "front": "to hide, conceal",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att ana",
      "front": "to suspect, anticipate, have a feeling",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att fördela",
      "front": "to distribute, to share, to split",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att undersöka",
      "front": "to examine, inspect, analyse, investigate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att syssla",
      "front": "to do, be busy/occupied with",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att störa",
      "front": "to disturb",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att reagera",
      "front": "to react",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att förvandla",
      "front": "to transform",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att överleva",
      "front": "to survive",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att återvända",
      "front": "to return",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att utreda",
      "front": "to investigate, analyse",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att dröja",
      "front": "to linger, last",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en närhet",
      "front": "a vicinity, a neighbourhood",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en varelse",
      "front": "a creature, a being",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en omröstning",
      "front": "a voting",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tråd",
      "front": "a thread",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en utvärdering",
      "front": "an evaluation",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett läger",
      "front": "a camp",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett mod",
      "front": "a courage, a bravery",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett fack",
      "front": "a box, slot. a trade, profession, a trade union",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett förlag",
      "front": "a publishing firm",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kost",
      "front": "a diet, a fare",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett testamente",
      "front": "a will",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en släkt",
      "front": "a family, a relation, relative",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett läkemedel",
      "front": "a pharmaceutical",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en motsats",
      "front": "a contradiction, an opposite",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en annons",
      "front": "an advert",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett byte",
      "front": "an exchange, a barter, a loot",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en företagare",
      "front": "an entrepeneur",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en gest",
      "front": "a gesture",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kamrat",
      "front": "a comrade, friend",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett blad",
      "front": "a blade, leaf (plant/book), a blade (tool/utensil)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en vana",
      "front": "a habit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett gymnasium",
      "front": "an upper secondary school",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett element",
      "front": "an element, a radiator",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett tvivel",
      "front": "a doubt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en anhörig",
      "front": "a relation, relative",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att plocka",
      "front": "to pick, to pluck",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att tränga",
      "front": "to drive, to push, to force",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att sticka",
      "front": "to stick, to put, to knit, to prick, col. to leave",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att medverka",
      "front": "to contribute to, take part in",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att vittna",
      "front": "to witness, testify, give evidence",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att överlämna",
      "front": "to deliver, hand/pass over, present, give",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att utforma",
      "front": "to design, shape, model, to draw up, formulate, to elaborate, work out in detail",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att uppfylla",
      "front": "to fulfill, perform, carry out, comply with, meet, satisfy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att variera",
      "front": "to vary, fluctuate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att förtjäna",
      "front": "to deserve",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att tävla",
      "front": "to compete (with/for)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att begränsa",
      "front": "to limit, to restrict",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att sakta",
      "front": "to slow down",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att lyda",
      "front": "to obey, comply with, answer to",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att lätta",
      "front": "to lighten, unburden, alleviate, ease",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att föreskriva",
      "front": "to prescribe, provide, direct, order, dictate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att klaga",
      "front": "to complain, to protest, to whine",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att anklaga",
      "front": "to accuse",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att neka",
      "front": "to deny, refuse",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att granska",
      "front": "to scrutinize, to inspect, to audit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att avslöja",
      "front": "to expose, uncover, debunk, reveal",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att sjunka",
      "front": "to sink, fall, to go down, to decrease",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att avbryta",
      "front": "to break/snap (off)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att fastna",
      "front": "to stick, to get stuck",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att bota",
      "front": "to cure, to heal",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att sträcka",
      "front": "to stretch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att knyta",
      "front": "to tie",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att slita",
      "front": "to wear, to tear",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mer eller mindre",
      "front": "more or less",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "eller hur",
      "front": "Don\u0027t you agree? Wouldn\u0027t you say?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "till sist",
      "front": "finally, at last",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "till slut",
      "front": "eventually, in the end",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en hel del",
      "front": "a good deal, a great many",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en massa",
      "front": "a mass; a mass/large amount \u003cof\u003e ...",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "i slutet",
      "front": "in the end",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "först och främst",
      "front": "first and foremost",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "just nu",
      "front": "right now, at this very moment",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "från och med nu",
      "front": "from here on out, from now on",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "till synes",
      "front": "seemingly",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lite grann",
      "front": "a little, to a small degree",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "så snart som möjligt",
      "front": "as soon as possible",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "för det mesta",
      "front": "for the most part",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "här och nu",
      "front": "here and now",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "inte längre",
      "front": "no longer, not anymore",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "så kallad",
      "front": "so called",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "forn",
      "front": "former, earlier",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dold",
      "front": "obscured, hidden, invisible",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ändlig",
      "front": "finite, limited",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "oändlig",
      "front": "infinite, measureless, boundless",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "noggrann",
      "front": "precise, scrupulous",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "försiktig",
      "front": "careful, cautious",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "rå",
      "front": "raw, crude, coarse, rough, brutal",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vild",
      "front": "wild",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "grym",
      "front": "fierce, ruthless, awful, cruel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "häftig",
      "front": "violent, energetic, hasty, excited",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "skadlig",
      "front": "harmful, unwholesome",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "elak",
      "front": "mean, cruel, malicious",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "förbannad",
      "front": "cursed, damned, blasted",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "besviken",
      "front": "disappointed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "giltig",
      "front": "valid",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "trång",
      "front": "tight, narrow, crowded",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fruktansvärd",
      "front": "dreadful, horrible, terrible",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "behaglig",
      "front": "pleasant, agreeable",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "obehaglig",
      "front": "unpleasant, disagreeable",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "besvärlig",
      "front": "difficult, troublesome",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "usel",
      "front": "wretched, miserable, worthless, very poor/bad",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "behörig",
      "front": "due, proper, qualified, competent",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lat",
      "front": "lazy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "pinsam",
      "front": "embarassing",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "löjlig",
      "front": "ridiculous",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "orimlig",
      "front": "unreasonable, absurd",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "förvirrad",
      "front": "confused",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lönsam",
      "front": "profitable",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "värdelös",
      "front": "worthless",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "förhoppningsvis",
      "front": "hopefully",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "på sätt och vis",
      "front": "in a way/sense",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bråttom",
      "front": "hurry, lack of time",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mittemot",
      "front": "opposite, facing",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "alltför (mycket/många) ...",
      "front": "far too (much/many) ...",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "omedelbart",
      "front": "immediately, as soon as possible",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "efteråt",
      "front": "afterwards",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bortifrån",
      "front": "from the direction of",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "likadant",
      "front": "similarly, in the same manner",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ingenstans",
      "front": "nowhere",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "småningom",
      "front": "after some time; sooner or later, eventually",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "så småningom",
      "front": "gradually, little by little, sooner or later",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "rimligtvis",
      "front": "reasonably",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tvärtom",
      "front": "on the contrary, in the opposite manner",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "numera",
      "front": "nowadays",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "alldeles",
      "front": "quite, perfectly, very",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "på gångavstånd",
      "front": "within walking distance",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "på förehand",
      "front": "beforehand, in advance",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "över huvud taget",
      "front": "at all, on the whole",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tvärs",
      "front": "across, abeam, perpendicularly",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dock",
      "front": "though, however, nonetheless",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "förstås",
      "front": "understandably, of course, naturally",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "såhär",
      "front": "like this",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sådär",
      "front": "like that",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sålunda",
      "front": "thus, in that way",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att rusa",
      "front": "to rush",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att lugna",
      "front": "to calm",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att förvåna",
      "front": "to surprise, astonish, amaze",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att tveka",
      "front": "to hesitate, to be in doubt, be doubtful",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att låtsas",
      "front": "to pretend",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att övertyga",
      "front": "to convince",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att reta",
      "front": "to tease, to annoy, to irritate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att beklaga",
      "front": "to be/feel sorry for someone",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att odla",
      "front": "to cultivate, till, to grow",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att försörja",
      "front": "to provide for",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att begripa",
      "front": "to comprehend, grasp",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att ramla",
      "front": "to fall, tumble, collapse, crash",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att svära",
      "front": "to swear",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att röka",
      "front": "to smoke",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att ångra",
      "front": "to regret, to repent",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att krossa",
      "front": "to crush",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att frukta",
      "front": "to fear, dread",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att fördöma",
      "front": "to condemn, damn, to blame",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att tända",
      "front": "to light, to turn/switch on",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att befria",
      "front": "to liberate, release from, to exempt from, to rid of",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att packa",
      "front": "to pack, to stow, to compress",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att uppföra",
      "front": "to bring forth, build; to perform, play, stage; to behave [reflexive]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att fria",
      "front": "to propose (marriage), to acquit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att bevaka",
      "front": "to guard; to watch, look after",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att skärpa",
      "front": "to sharpen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att krypa",
      "front": "to creep, crawl",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att smyga",
      "front": "to sneak, to creep",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att hugga",
      "front": "to slash, to cut",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att brista",
      "front": "to burst, rupture; to break, snap, split",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att skänka",
      "front": "to donate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en spets",
      "front": "a point, a tip, an end, a nib",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ton",
      "front": "a ton, a tone, note, a shade",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett medvetande",
      "front": "a consciousness",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en slav",
      "front": "a slave",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en vinkel",
      "front": "an angle",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en andning",
      "front": "(a) breathing, (a) respiration",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en stress",
      "front": "(a) stress",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett skämt",
      "front": "a joke",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett samvete",
      "front": "a conscience",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kant",
      "front": "an edge",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en rutin",
      "front": "an experience, a routine",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en skylt",
      "front": "a sign, signpost",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ruta",
      "front": "a square, a panel, a pane, a screen, a box",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en paus",
      "front": "a pause, break, intermission",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett dagis",
      "front": "a day care, nursery",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett kvarter",
      "front": "a block, a distract, a quarter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en skönhet",
      "front": "a beauty",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tonåring",
      "front": "a teenager",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett elände",
      "front": "a misery, wretchedness, a wretch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en förare",
      "front": "a driver",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en evighet",
      "front": "an eternity",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett humör",
      "front": "a mood, a temper",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ekonom",
      "front": "an economist",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en diagnos",
      "front": "a diagnosis",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett självmord",
      "front": "a suicide",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett karl",
      "front": "a man, fellow, guy, chap",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en stuga",
      "front": "a cottage, cabin, small house",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en längtan",
      "front": "(a) longing",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en fröken",
      "front": "a teacher; young lady; an unmarried woman",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en brottsling",
      "front": "a criminal, felon",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett änka",
      "front": "a widow",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett bygge",
      "front": "a building [under construction]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en förort",
      "front": "a suburb",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en last",
      "front": "a load, a cargo, freight",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en lastbil",
      "front": "a lorry, truck",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en besvikelse",
      "front": "a disappointment",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en skräck",
      "front": "a terror, fright, dread, horror",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en klapp",
      "front": "a pat, tap",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en krog",
      "front": "an inn, a pub",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett inköp",
      "front": "a purchase",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ansökning",
      "front": "an application",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en byrå",
      "front": "a chest of drawers",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett bekymmer",
      "front": "a trouble, worry; a difficulty",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en lucka",
      "front": "a gap, hatch, gate; a hole, opening",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en panik",
      "front": "a panic",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en avslutning",
      "front": "a completion, concluding, conclusion, finishing (off); a termination",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en pjäs",
      "front": "a play, a piece (in a boardgame)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en dokumentär",
      "front": "a documentary",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en uppsägning",
      "front": "notice (to quit, of removal; termination; cancellation; withdrawal)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett bråk",
      "front": "a fraction, noise, row, racket, hullabaloo, quarell, fuss, trouble",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) sprit",
      "front": "(a) spirit, (a) liquor, (an) alcohol",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "beroende",
      "front": "dependant",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "stadig",
      "front": "steady, stable, sturdy, durable",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tillåten",
      "front": "allowed, permitted, lawful",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "förnuftig",
      "front": "rational, sensible, reasonable",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "modig",
      "front": "brave",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "upprörd",
      "front": "upset, agitated",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "blek",
      "front": "pale, faint, white",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "seg",
      "front": "tough, viscous, sticky, leathery, longwinded",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dyrbar",
      "front": "precious, valuable",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "blank",
      "front": "shiny, reflective",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "platt",
      "front": "flat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "idiotisk",
      "front": "idiotic",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fientlig",
      "front": "hostile",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tokig",
      "front": "crazy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "förmögen",
      "front": "rich, capable",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vidrig",
      "front": "repulsive, hateful, obnoxious, odious, horrid",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "skum",
      "front": "dark, dusky, misty, suspicious, disreputable",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dyster",
      "front": "gloomy, dismal, depressing, glum",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "trasig",
      "front": "ragged, tattered, torn, frayed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vansinnig",
      "front": "insane, demented, deranged",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "krånglig",
      "front": "complicated, troublesome, awkward",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "varifrån",
      "front": "where from",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "överallt",
      "front": "everywhere",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "exempelvis",
      "front": "for example",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "allmänt",
      "front": "generally",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "härefter",
      "front": "after this, from now, subsequently",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "därefter",
      "front": "after that, subsequently, according to that",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "heller",
      "front": "neither",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hellre",
      "front": "rather, preferably",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "extremt",
      "front": "extremely",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "inrikes",
      "front": "home, domestic, national",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "utrikes",
      "front": "foreign, abroad",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ombord",
      "front": "onboard",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "säkert",
      "front": "surely, safely",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dagligen",
      "front": "daily",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "veckovis",
      "front": "weekly",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "extra",
      "front": "extra",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "årligen",
      "front": "yearly",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "självklart",
      "front": "of course, obviously",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "artigt",
      "front": "politely, courteously",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dittills",
      "front": "up to then, until that time",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "cirka",
      "front": "circa, roughly, around",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "just",
      "front": "just, precisely, exactly",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "i varje fall",
      "front": "in any case, at any rate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "i övermorgon",
      "front": "the day after tomorrow",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "i går kväll",
      "front": "last night",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "förresten",
      "front": "by the way, incidentally",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "emellertid",
      "front": "however",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "direkt",
      "front": "directly, immediately",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vidare",
      "front": "further",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att stava",
      "front": "to spell",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att växla",
      "front": "to change, exchange, switch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att anstränga",
      "front": "to strain, to exert",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att vifta",
      "front": "to wag, to wave",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att böja",
      "front": "to bow, to bend, to inflect",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att snurra",
      "front": "to spin, rotate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att nicka",
      "front": "to nod",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att stirra",
      "front": "to stare",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att viga",
      "front": "to marry, consecrate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att förvara",
      "front": "to keep, store",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att tömma",
      "front": "to empty",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att supa",
      "front": "to drink (alcohol) [excessively]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att bråka",
      "front": "to quarrel, to cause trouble, to break",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att bekänna",
      "front": "to confess, avow, profess",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att inbilla",
      "front": "to imagine",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att smitta",
      "front": "to infect, give/pass on; to be catching, coming down with",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att tjata",
      "front": "to nag, harp",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en panna",
      "front": "a forehead, a pan",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en hall",
      "front": "a hall",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en förteckning",
      "front": "a catalogue, register",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en regissör",
      "front": "a director, producer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en insändare",
      "front": "a corespondant, a letter to the press",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en behörighet",
      "front": "a competence, competency, a qualification",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en vrede",
      "front": "a wrath, fury, rage",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en slöja",
      "front": "a vail, (a) fog",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en knut",
      "front": "a knot",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en befrielse",
      "front": "a liberation, relief, deliverance",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett skal",
      "front": "a shell, a peel, rind, a husk",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en källare",
      "front": "a cellar",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en firma",
      "front": "a firm, business, company",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en bensin",
      "front": "(a) gasoline, (a) petrol",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en svält",
      "front": "(a) starvation",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en beställning",
      "front": "an order, request",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett kloster",
      "front": "a monastery",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en förvåning",
      "front": "a surprise, asonishment, amazement",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett schema",
      "front": "a schedule, a scheme",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en mask",
      "front": "a worm",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tröst",
      "front": "a comfort, a consolation",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en succé",
      "front": "a hit, a success",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en remiss",
      "front": "a referral",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en robot",
      "front": "a robot; a guided missile",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ask",
      "front": "a small box",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en balkong",
      "front": "a balcony",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en bänk",
      "front": "a bench, seat, desk, a workbench, worktop",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en termin",
      "front": "a term, semester, an installment, a due date, a period",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en sal",
      "front": "a large (meeting) room",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett modersmål",
      "front": "a mother-tongue, native language",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en sedel",
      "front": "a banknote",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en merit",
      "front": "a qualification, recommendation",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en möda",
      "front": "a hardship, a trouble, a toil",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en korridor",
      "front": "a corridor",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en utflykt",
      "front": "an excursion, outing, trip, a picnic",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett skräp",
      "front": "(a) {scrap}, garbage, junk",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett chips",
      "front": "(a) crisps, (a) chips",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett fläck",
      "front": "a fleck, spot, speck, blotch, patch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en sjöman",
      "front": "a sailor, seaman, mariner",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett stryk",
      "front": "a beating",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en feber",
      "front": "a fever",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en flock",
      "front": "a flock, a murder of crows",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en magi",
      "front": "a magic",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en grotta",
      "front": "a cave, cavern, a grotto",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en nacke",
      "front": "(a) back of the head, nape of the neck",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en avsky",
      "front": "a loathing",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en lyx",
      "front": "a luxury, an extravagance, a magnificence, splendour, richness",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en mössa",
      "front": "a cap, hat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "knepig",
      "front": "tricky",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sval",
      "front": "cool, chilly",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "stel",
      "front": "stiff, inflexible, overly strict or formal",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hotfull",
      "front": "threatening, menacing, ominous",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fånig",
      "front": "silly, stupid, foolish",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "förälskad",
      "front": "in love",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lärorik",
      "front": "instructive",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "döv",
      "front": "deaf, hard of hearing",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "misstänksam",
      "front": "suspicious",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "berusad",
      "front": "drunk",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "illamående",
      "front": "sick, unwell",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "otillåten",
      "front": "forbidden; unlawful, illicit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "plågsam",
      "front": "torturous, agonising",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "stökig",
      "front": "messy, untidy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "eländig",
      "front": "wretched, miserable, rotten, lousy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "trög",
      "front": "sluggish, slow, dull, inert, stiff",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mager",
      "front": "lean, skinny",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "svettig",
      "front": "sweaty, sweating, perspiring",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "gränslös",
      "front": "boundless, limitless, immense, tremendous",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "genomskinlig",
      "front": "transparent, see-through",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "myndig",
      "front": "being in the age of majority, authoritative",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "matt",
      "front": "matte, weak",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att avsky",
      "front": "to loathe, to detest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att plåga",
      "front": "to plague, torment, to worry, to pester, to bore",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att utvisa",
      "front": "to show, indicate, to send off",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att begrava",
      "front": "to bury",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att operera",
      "front": "to operate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att skälla",
      "front": "to bark, to scold, tell off",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att släcka",
      "front": "to turn off, to extinguish",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att inviga",
      "front": "to inaugarate, dedicate, consecrate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att svälta",
      "front": "to (let) starve",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att vädja",
      "front": "to appeal",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att övertala",
      "front": "to persuade, to prevail upon, induce",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att smälla",
      "front": "to bang, knock, smack, slam",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att diskriminera",
      "front": "to discriminate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att såga",
      "front": "to saw",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att färga",
      "front": "to colour, dye, paint; to influence, impact",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att renovera",
      "front": "to renovate, do up, restore",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en bebis",
      "front": "a baby",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett fat",
      "front": "a saucer, plate, a barrel, cask, keg",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en fästning",
      "front": "a fort, fortress",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en uniform",
      "front": "a uniform",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en fasa",
      "front": "a fear",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en tapet",
      "front": "a wallpaper",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en salong",
      "front": "a parlor, lounge, saloon",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en slöseri",
      "front": "a wastefulness, an extravagance",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en psalm",
      "front": "a hymn, a psalm",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kår",
      "front": "a corps, union, a chill, shiver",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett lås",
      "front": "a lock",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en lukt",
      "front": "a smell, an odour, a scent",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en nybörjare",
      "front": "a beginner",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett andetag",
      "front": "a breath",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en handledare",
      "front": "an instructor, supervisor",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en förlossning",
      "front": "a childbirth, delivery of a baby",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en parkering",
      "front": "a carpark",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en dräkt",
      "front": "a costume",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en galenskap",
      "front": "a madness",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en skörd",
      "front": "a harvest",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en galning",
      "front": "a lunatic, madman",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en näve",
      "front": "a handful",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en ättling",
      "front": "a descendant",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en snickare",
      "front": "a carpenter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en snubbe",
      "front": "a dude [old-fashioned]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en befallning",
      "front": "an order, command, a bidding",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en pedagog",
      "front": "a pedagogue, an educator",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en syndare",
      "front": "a sinner, an offender",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en riddare",
      "front": "a knight",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en förvandling",
      "front": "a transformation, metamorphosis",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en spis",
      "front": "a stove",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en hetta",
      "front": "(a) heat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en hjälm",
      "front": "a helmet",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett geni",
      "front": "a genie",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en mottagning",
      "front": "a reception, consulting room",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "(en) svett",
      "front": "(a) sweat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en skrik",
      "front": "a scream, a shout, a yell",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett formulär",
      "front": "a form, a formula, convention",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett bälte",
      "front": "a belt [physical \u0026 abstract]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en stövel",
      "front": "a boot",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en buske",
      "front": "a bush, shrub",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en asfalt",
      "front": "(an) asphalt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en stolpe",
      "front": "a pole, a post",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en försäljare",
      "front": "a salesperson",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en rullstol",
      "front": "a wheelchair",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en brunn",
      "front": "a well",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en förolämpning",
      "front": "an insult",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en skymning",
      "front": "a dusk",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett farväl",
      "front": "a farewell",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en nykomling",
      "front": "a newcomer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett kuvert",
      "front": "an envelope",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kavaj",
      "front": "a fancy/sports jacket",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en barnmorska",
      "front": "a midwife",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en gröt",
      "front": "(a) porridge",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en högtalare",
      "front": "a loudspeaker",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en nål",
      "front": "a needle, a syringe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett ordspråk",
      "front": "a saying, a proverb",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en lämplighet",
      "front": "a suitability, appropriateness, an eligibility",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en trottoar",
      "front": "a pavement, sidewalk",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en illamående",
      "front": "a feeling of sickness",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en kappa",
      "front": "a coat, an outdoor jacket",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett kvitto",
      "front": "a receipt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett päron",
      "front": "a pear",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en frisör",
      "front": "a barber, hairdresser",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett gräl",
      "front": "a quarrel, squabble, tiff",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett garn",
      "front": "a yarn",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ett garage",
      "front": "a garage",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en hyresvärd",
      "front": "a landlord",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "en hyresvärdinna",
      "front": "a landlady",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ogiltig",
      "front": "invalid",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "medvetslös",
      "front": "unconscious",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "artig",
      "front": "polite, courteous",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "klumpig",
      "front": "clumsy, awkward; clumpy, lumpy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "yr",
      "front": "dizzy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bortskämd",
      "front": "spoilt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "självsäker",
      "front": "presumptuous, self-confident",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "betydlig",
      "front": "significant",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "frånskild",
      "front": "divorced",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bullrig",
      "front": "noisy, loud",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kraftlös",
      "front": "week, feeble, powerless",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bildad",
      "front": "educated, refined",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fasansfull",
      "front": "appaling, gruesome, ghastly",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fyllig",
      "front": "plump, detailed, rich",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "gapig",
      "front": "loudmouthed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "generad",
      "front": "embarassed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "inåtriktad",
      "front": "introverted",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "utåtriktad",
      "front": "extroverted",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kvav",
      "front": "stuffy, suffocating, stifling",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sliten",
      "front": "worn, shabby",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "taggig",
      "front": "prickly, thorny",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fånig",
      "front": "stupid, foolish [colloquial]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vinglig",
      "front": "wobbly",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ostadig",
      "front": "unsteady, unstable, unsettled",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dammig",
      "front": "dusty",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vresig",
      "front": "cross, bad-tempered",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "snål",
      "front": "stingy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "oduglig",
      "front": "incapable, incompetent",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "avskyvärd",
      "front": "detestable, abominable",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "försvarslös",
      "front": "defenseless",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "omedelbar",
      "front": "immediate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "inslagen",
      "front": "wrapped",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "otålig",
      "front": "impatient",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ilsken",
      "front": "angry, mad, furious",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "skrynklig",
      "front": "creased, wrinkled",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "förvriden",
      "front": "twisted, distorted, contorted",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "skräckslagen",
      "front": "terror-struck, horror-stricken",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "olåst",
      "front": "unlocked",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "häpen",
      "front": "astonished, astounded",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tålig",
      "front": "durable; patient",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ursinnig",
      "front": "furious, infuriated",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "utmattad",
      "front": "worn out, exhausted",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ohygglig",
      "front": "dreadful, ghastly, gruesome, hideous",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "avbruten",
      "front": "broken, aborted, interrupted",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "uthungrad",
      "front": "famished, starving",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ödslig",
      "front": "desolate, deserted, dreary",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "febrig",
      "front": "feverish",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hopvikt",
      "front": "folded",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hysterisk",
      "front": "hysteric(al)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "efterbliven",
      "front": "backwards [derogatory]",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "upphetsad",
      "front": "excited, agitated, worked up",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att utbyta",
      "front": "to exchange, to replace",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att trösta",
      "front": "to comfort, to console",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att jämställa",
      "front": "to place on a level/an equal footing/in the same category as",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att anteckna",
      "front": "to note, to write down",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att klappa",
      "front": "to pat, tap, clap, to beat, throb",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att förakta",
      "front": "to despise, disdain, hold in contempt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att utbrista",
      "front": "to exclaim, cry, burst out",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att angå",
      "front": "to concern",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att skina",
      "front": "to shine",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att skoja",
      "front": "to fool, to cheat, to joke, to prank",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att strypa",
      "front": "to strangle, choke, throttle",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att sucka",
      "front": "to (heave a) sigh",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att uträtta",
      "front": "to do, carry out, to accomplish",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att spärra",
      "front": "to block, close, obstruct, put out of service",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att avskeda",
      "front": "to dismiss",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att knuffa",
      "front": "to push, shove, jostle, shoulder, elbow, nudge",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att blinka",
      "front": "to blink",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att stråla",
      "front": "to beam, shine, to be radiant",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att krocka",
      "front": "to crash, collide",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att råna",
      "front": "to rob, steal",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att stressa",
      "front": "to stress",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att omfamna",
      "front": "to embrace",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att klia",
      "front": "to itch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att förolämpa",
      "front": "to insult, offend",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att lossna",
      "front": "to loosen, to come off/undone",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att svida",
      "front": "to sting, ache, burn, hurt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att mala",
      "front": "to grind on, speak ceaselessly",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att förhöra",
      "front": "to interrogate, question, cross-examine",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att grubbla",
      "front": "to ponder",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att darra",
      "front": "to shiver, to tremble",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att möblera",
      "front": "to furnish",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att förvrida",
      "front": "to twist, to distort, to contort",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "skrämd",
      "front": "terrified, frightened, startled",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sorgsen",
      "front": "sorrowful, woeful, melancholy, mournful",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "egendomlig",
      "front": "peculiar, odd, remarkable",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "överlycklig",
      "front": "overjoyed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hatisk",
      "front": "spiteful, hateful",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "olydig",
      "front": "disobedient",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sansad",
      "front": "calm, collected, composed, level-headed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "utfattig",
      "front": "destitute, miserably poor",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "färggrann",
      "front": "richly/brightly coloured",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "påklädd",
      "front": "dressed",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fläckig",
      "front": "flecked, spotted, speckled; stained, blotched, patched",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sinnessjuk",
      "front": "mad, crazy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dimmig",
      "front": "foggy, misty, hazy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "rar",
      "front": "kind, sweet, pleasant",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "begagnad",
      "front": "used, pre-owned, secondhand",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "att vara/bli snuvig",
      "front": "to have/catch a cold",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "rastlös",
      "front": "restless",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "oregelbunden",
      "front": "irregular, erratic, anomalous",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "åtkomlig",
      "front": "accessible, within reach",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "oåtkomlig",
      "front": "inaccessible, unapproachable, unobtainable",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "självisk",
      "front": "selfish",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "egoistisk",
      "front": "egoistic, selfish",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hållbar",
      "front": "durable, lasting, hardwearing",
      "level": 2
    }
  ],
  "file": "Duolingo_Swedish",
  "name": "Duolingo Swedish",
  "back": "sv",
  "description": "Learning Swedish for English speakers"
  
}